<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-03-17T23:05:21.477Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:99063474310237184) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:99063474310237184+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T23:05:21.478Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safety Note+ Pro]]></title>
        <id>Safety Note+ Pro-1742252540459</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/safety-note-pro/id460661291?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T23:02:20.459Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺179,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/safety-note-pro/id460661291?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/29/06/41/290641d6-1d49-9938-5ce0-0c15eb7cdc07/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺179,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Introducing Safety Note+: Keep Your Most Private Notes Secure

Have you ever experienced the frustration of lending someone your phone, only to have them intrude on your personal information? We understand the discomfort that comes with it. That's why we created Safety Note+. With this powerful app, you can now safeguard your private notes from unauthorized access effortlessly.

Key Features:

• Advanced security system: Utilizing state-of-the-art technology to protect your notes
• Passcode protection: Quickly and easily secure your most private and sensitive notes with a passcode only known to you
• Biometric support: Unlock the app using TouchID or FaceID for added convenience
• Intruder report: Capture photos of unauthorized individuals attempting to access your app
• Decoy password: Conceal your real privacy with a decoy password
• Folder-specific passcode locking: Enhance security by applying passcode protection to individual folders
• Dot pattern lock style: Opt for a higher level of security with the dot pattern lock style
• Multiple lock designs: Choose from three stylish and user-friendly lock designs without compromising security
• Intuitive interface: Selectable themes and an easy-to-use interface make managing your notes a breeze
• Note organization: Create, sort, move, and copy notes within folders
• Backup and sharing options: Back up notes to your computer via iTunes file sharing or iCloud, and share notes between iOS devices with Safety Note+ installed via Bluetooth or Wi-Fi
• Additional features: Auto-save, note search, email notes, and full orientation support
• Universal compatibility: Developed for both iPhone and iPad, requiring a single purchase

Your privacy matters. With Safety Note+, you can confidently secure your personal information. Customize your passcode style, protect individual folders, and experience the peace of mind that comes with complete control over your private notes.

Download Safety Note+ now and ensure that what goes into Safety Note+ remains for your eyes only.

Visit us at:
Website: https://sixbytes.io
Twitter: https://twitter.com/SixbytesApp
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/sixbytesapp

For more information, please refer to our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy:
Terms of service: https://sixbytes.io/assets/terms-of-service.pdf
Privacy policy: https://sixbytes.io/assets/privacy-policy.pdf
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/32/9b/ec/329bec07-06b0-616d-a0ef-469100d60caf/48ef49cf-d737-45c7-800a-40d960458f41_1.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/32/df/f4/32dff459-3fd7-d49e-8ca1-e5c65737d4c0/7a2f8d74-5471-4f4b-a547-b00f01d4dbe6_2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/61/19/d4/6119d4ec-a67d-d31d-0432-31448f74bde8/d6f23d4c-bdc4-488d-9412-c0def307671b_3.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/7c/c7/4e/7cc74ea0-c474-fd63-87f5-13d4b698e21f/f9d87e43-32ba-46ed-8509-cc5948831914_4.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/8f/56/11/8f56118b-c480-f65f-8bd5-faa27992306f/daafb7d9-15bb-4511-a6fc-643c7cb3f247_5.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/20/64/6c/20646c3f-2562-4870-38aa-2d09a2ccbfd6/7506752e-c878-478b-a21e-cc98d15a9fd5_6.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/96/9e/5b/969e5b5e-6a53-1a89-27d2-63ec91584d4a/9445e5b4-e396-4d04-9335-2a7ee164253e_7.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/21/c5/fc/21c5fc25-ebee-5bb4-f315-595d5c237148/e9e762d2-3f5d-4ef3-a7ab-33124ec0623d_1.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/97/68/1f/97681fed-10a5-5708-f2e8-f28e8f69b1c7/b199c8f7-ac75-47b4-b15c-031d8e4bbcce_2.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/9e/f8/b6/9ef8b68a-1f63-bce6-0b66-4ed1e601dca8/ee0a1e60-9a81-4ea8-a713-72f9236fea62_3.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/3c/46/3d/3c463d0c-7832-84e3-b633-b1bebbe1fda3/c142eebe-bb19-4fa7-82ec-08a39105662f_4.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/e0/e3/a4/e0e3a471-7eb7-d520-d9cf-53806cfc3b34/5bd71368-68c5-4cd2-ad48-6817f8275746_5.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/40/ee/67/40ee672e-6051-6ed0-cd1d-f36f5dd7fbdc/bdc2003c-2e32-4926-8587-6e282cea9254_6.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/55/c7/7a/55c77a62-b27b-707c-e837-65f8ec28aad5/59ca110a-c0fa-4dc7-b261-efcad496eba6_7.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RAIN RADAR ° live weather maps]]></title>
        <id>RAIN RADAR ° live weather maps-1742252540459</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/rain-radar-live-weather-maps/id488674899?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T23:02:20.459Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺599,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/rain-radar-live-weather-maps/id488674899?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/44/a6/eb/44a6ebc2-0045-22bb-5c81-8cbfcc93bfb0/AppIcon-Full-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺599,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Imagine that the entire globe is at your fingertips. Never before has getting weather information been as exciting and interactive as it is in the “Weather Now” application.
Amazingly beautiful 3D images of our planet draws your attention for so long that you may forget that the application has other useful features that allows you easy access to precise, global weather information.

The main features of “Weather Now” are the “home screen” and the forecast page with a unique way of scaling the charts. On the “home screen”, you can get information on the selected location such as local time and current weather with detailed weather conditions, and, of course, an incredibly beautiful three-dimensional image of the globe with realistic-looking atmosphere, the sun and the stars. You can manually turn it, increase and decrease its size, run the slow spinning animation or stop it. Installed in a cradle or dock station, the application can run as a screensaver, attracting your friends and fellows.

The weather forecast is provided by CustomWeather, Inc, an American weather provider of global weather information for over 11 years. CustomWeather is a leader in technology and meteorological innovation, providing local weather information to companies and application developers around the world.

The current weather data is gathered from thousands of professionally installed and maintained weather stations installed mostly at airports. WeatherNow only shows current weather from stations that have reported local weather conditions within the past hour. Current weather data is refreshed every 30 minutes; that is twice as frequent as most other weather providers can offer. Unique 48-hour forecasts from over 80,000 locations around the world provide a level of coverage and detail that simply cannot be found elsewhere.

Current weather information includes: description, air temperature, wind direction and force, humidity, dew point, pressure, visibility, as well as comfort index with reference to current weather conditions. 
Detailed weather forecast information includes: description, day and night air temperature, wind direction and force, humidity, UV index, probability of precipitation, and comfort index with reference to current weather conditions.

Features:
• Chic 3D “home screen” with high-quality real-time image of the earth, atmosphere, the stars and the sun 
• Weather Maps, include: Clouds Cover, Precipitation's, Pressure, Wind and Temperature
• Current temperature on the icon badge
• Easily select different cities using the city carousel with national flags 
• 15-day forecast chart with detailed daily weather conditions, independent day and night temperature charts 
• 48-hour hourly forecast with detailed information with real-time changing of chart step
• Database of 80 000 cities with weather information, quick look-up and automatic detection of location
• Extended application setting for best application experience
• Current time and date for selected location
• Sunrise and sunset time, UI Index
• Multi Language support
• Share weather info use your Twitter account
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/a3/3d/2a/a33d2a55-48a0-198c-5b98-6f1dd4cb2126/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/16/b2/96/16b296cb-a323-c26c-1c67-8d336eaade89/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/72/37/90/723790d9-642f-995f-5469-1e588dc81498/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/0d/3f/2d/0d3f2de0-3a41-ebad-bb58-e53b811f4c3d/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/5c/1b/62/5c1b625d-5f1f-e349-1560-7c82a12cf0fe/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/9d/59/61/9d596154-9d65-80c9-ab53-83ffd40e6ef8/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/df/13/66/df13660d-b292-b476-d9e2-e0b2e010d0ba/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/43/88/9c/43889c88-ab93-e998-d855-c08f4fb805db/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/0d/72/7c/0d727cce-b561-e9d2-a7db-3a3de3baa490/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/a3/c4/ea/a3c4ead7-014d-f4c2-af52-4e2eecd97377/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/c7/3b/f1/c73bf143-8967-2204-b939-40b74f669980/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/17/0f/e4/170fe4c4-a239-274a-d507-99efff510706/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>