<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-04-28T23:21:11.009Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:99063474310237184) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:99063474310237184+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:21:11.010Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codenames]]></title>
        <id>Codenames-1745881340255</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/codenames/id1055650930?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:02:20.255Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺229,99 → ₺129,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/codenames/id1055650930?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/31/1b/bb/311bbb3a-056f-7b52-2fd3-4bdee761f64e/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-11-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺229,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺129,99</strong>
</b><span>(₺129,99 ~ ₺229,99)</span>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Step into the thrilling world of spies and secret agents! Codenames App brings the beloved word association game to your mobile device in a dynamic and engaging new way. Decipher your spymaster's one-word clues, connect the right words, and contact all your agents before the opposing team does to claim victory. This digital adaptation captures all the excitement of one of the most popular board games worldwide, now optimized for your pocket.


A Game of Clever Connections and Quick Thinking
---------------------------------------------------
Codenames App is an asynchronous multiplayer experience where two rival teams face off in a battle of wits and wordplay. Your objective? Find the best way to link as many words as possible with a single clue, outsmart the opposing team, and lead your side to victory. Whether you're teaming up with friends, playing against other secret agents, or going solo, the Codenames App offers endless strategic fun for everyone.


Inspired by the Iconic Board Game
----------------------------------
Join the millions of players worldwide who have fallen in love with Codenames. Designed by Vlaada Chvátil, the Codenames App is the latest addition to the renowned Codenames family. Experience the game that has captivated people of all ages and become a cultural phenomenon.


More Content, More Fun
-------------------------
While staying true to the original’s clever word-based puzzle mechanics, the Codenames App goes beyond the table, bringing you thousands of new thematic words and engaging twists on gameplay. Enjoy new modes, unlock exciting upgrades, and collect achievements as you explore deeper into the world of Codenames.


Play Anytime, Anywhere
------------------------
With our asynchronous multiplayer system, you can play at your own pace without the need to wait for others to be online at the same time. Each player has up to 24 hours to take their turn, so the game fits perfectly into your schedule. Start multiple matches, challenge new players, or enjoy special daily solo challenges.


Build Your Secret Agent Career
-------------------------------
Rise through the ranks of your spy agency, leveling up and earning rewards along the way. Prove your mastery in word association puzzles, unlock unique gadgets, new game modes, and expand your personal word collection. Showcase your skills and become the ultimate spymaster!


Connect and Compete with Friends
-----------------------------------
Challenge your friends or find new opponents from around the globe through our matchmaking system. Share your achievements, unlocked modes, and special word collections in friendly matches. Whether you're playing casually or climbing the competitive ranks, Codenames App is all about having fun with words.

Codenames App - The Board Game You Love, Reimagined for Your Mobile!
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cytus II]]></title>
        <id>Cytus II-1745881340255</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/cytus-ii/id1290687550?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:02:20.255Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺99,99 → Free<br/>Memory Unit [A1]: ₺229,99 → ₺99,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/cytus-ii/id1290687550?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/33/7b/bc/337bbce4-1f3d-b9ff-e7bd-561633d222bf/AppIcon-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺99,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b><span>(Free ~ ₺99,99)</span>）
</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Memory Unit [A1]：</strong><span>₺229,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺99,99</strong>
</b><span>(₺99,99 ~ ₺229,99)</span>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  "Cytus II" is a music rhythm game created by Rayark Games. It's our fourth rhythm game title, following the footsteps of three global successes, "Cytus", "DEEMO" and "VOEZ". This sequel to "Cytus" brings back the original staff and is a product of hardwork and devotion. 

In the future, humans have redefined internet development and connections. We can now easily sync the real world with the internet world, changing life as we have known for thousands of years. 

In the mega virtual internet space cyTus, there exists a mysterious DJ legend Æsir. His music has an irresistible charm; people fall madly in love with his music. Rumor has it that every note and beat of his music hits the audiences in 
the depths of their souls. 

One day, Æsir, who had never shown his face before, suddenly announced that he will be holding the first mega virtual concert —— Æsir-FEST and will invite a top idol singer and a popular DJ as opening performances. The instant the ticket sales began, an unprecedented rush occurred. Everyone wanted to see Æsir's real face. 

On the day of the FEST,  millions of people were connected to the event. At one hour before the event started,  the previous world record for most simultaneous connection was smashed. The whole city was on its feet, waiting for Æsir to descent from the skies...

Game Features:

- The unique "Active Judgement Line" rhythm game playstyle
Tap the notes as the judgement line hits them to achieve a high score. Through five different kinds of notes and the judgement line that actively adjusts its speed according to the beat, the gameplay experience is further combined with the music. Players can easily immerse themselves in the songs. 

- A total of 250+ high-quality songs (50+ in base game, 200+ as IAP)
The game includes songs by composers from all across the world, Japan, Korea, the US, Europe, Taiwan and more. Through the characters, players get to play songs from different genres including but not limited to: electronic, rock and classical. We are confident that this game will live up to the hype and expectations.

- Over 800 different charts
Over 800 different charts designed, from easy to hard. The rich game content can satisfy players of different levels. Experience exciting challenges and enjoyment through the sensation of your fingertips. 

- Explore the virtual internet world with the game's characters
The one-of-a-kind story system "iM" will lead the players and the in-game characters to slowly piece together the story and world behind "Cytus II". Reveal the truth of the story with a rich, cinematic visual experience. 

PAFF (CV:上坂すみれ Sumire Uesaka)
NEKO (CV:花守ゆみり Yumiri Hanamori)
Xenon (CV:関智一 Tomokazu Seki)
ConneR (CV:竹内栄治 Eiji Takeuchi)
Cherry (CV:ファイルーズあい Fairouz Ai)
Nora (CV:石見舞菜香 Manaka Iwami)
Ivy (CV:河瀬茉希 Maki Kawase)
Vanessa (CV:楠木ともり Tomori Kusunoki)
Rin (CV:能登麻美子 Mamiko Noto)

*************************************************************
Cytus II will perform a connection authentication for its In-app purchases from time to time.
If you discover during the authentication period that your IAP was lost due to your device not connecting to the internet, 
please make sure your device is connected to the internet. Afterwards, click "Restore Purchases" to recover your IAP.
*************************************************************
※ This game contains mild violence and vulgar language. Suitable for users age 15 and above.
※ This game contains additional in-app purchases. Please purchased base on personal interest and ability. Do not overspend.
※ Please pay attention to your game time and avoid addiction.
※ Please do not use this game for gambling or other illegal purposes.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/f8/92/7a/f8927ad3-9755-c2e5-e69b-a483d53438d7/f4904806-2fab-48b0-ab80-244f0cd99503_2208X1242.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/bf/40/07/bf4007c4-8f91-abd5-e476-a79f4dd8c3bf/1d15539f-bbcd-41c1-9765-4acbefe99f54__U5c0d_U7acb-2208x1242.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/c1/62/fd/c162fd6c-b5ba-628b-eceb-8f52e624626a/12094d74-c35a-4830-a43b-02073c822f5f_5.5_001_0000.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/80/b1/ca/80b1ca33-2e5e-2b7a-a8fe-733c54f42b97/7b003a02-69f6-45f0-b2b7-5af9fad101e2__U9078_U6b4c-2208x1242.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/0f/69/ca/0f69caf3-aa63-1935-2b4f-875f722568a2/8ba67d51-0f49-4804-9362-013daae72b41_2208X1242.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/6d/64/24/6d6424cb-76ad-469c-72f6-23872a705970/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/87/76/97/877697dc-86c6-4a6a-3980-b5c627f5c310/1d19606d-0be5-40dd-84ca-e25f8b50346b_Screenshot94.png/406x228bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/ba/06/b7/ba06b7c5-48f0-7d7c-f21b-d37aad05f76d/f30625eb-0216-4a83-93b2-748f6373151e_2732X2048.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/36/3c/71/363c7135-27f2-265e-8d4b-997c402c4d7f/d07b2c9d-0d63-477a-a768-423829e7e5bd__U5c0d_U7acb-2732x2048.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/4f/3c/a2/4f3ca2f6-5c4b-859e-754a-6b5c1d7b74f0/aebbb62d-199a-46fe-9f87-b8c86007f70c_IPAD_004_0001.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/f8/2f/5a/f82f5a3f-6e92-5ecb-10d8-e066aa673c68/34c62ea0-0255-4c4a-991d-db271f044e03__U9078_U6b4c-2732x2048.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/0c/c6/b4/0cc6b4c1-0652-d50f-2645-2c86e2d736aa/6e0644ae-650d-4272-80bb-275a7a6d5b0e_2732X2048.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/77/7e/44/777e44b3-b9b5-0217-c01f-659b55b183bf/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/8a/0e/12/8a0e12fd-f6aa-9117-f50c-1d64dcdcb3bb/487511c0-8cb1-4d4a-b888-2d671a000878_Screenshot93.png/552x414bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[召喚騎士團]]></title>
        <id>召喚騎士團-1745881340255</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/%E5%8F%AC%E5%96%9A%E9%A8%8E%E5%A3%AB%E5%9C%98/id6471947612?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-28T23:02:20.255Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[劇情模式: ₺229,99 → ₺179,99<br/>自由模式: ₺229,99 → ₺179,99<br/>故事模式+自由模式合集: ₺399,99 → ₺299,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/%E5%8F%AC%E5%96%9A%E9%A8%8E%E5%A3%AB%E5%9C%98/id6471947612?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/f6/c5/50/f6c550b0-ffd9-d2be-cdbd-6435eac03040/AppIcon-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>Discount Information</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>劇情模式：</strong><span>₺229,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺179,99</strong>
</b><span>(₺179,99 ~ ₺229,99)</span>
  </li><li>
    <strong>自由模式：</strong><span>₺229,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺179,99</strong>
</b><span>(₺179,99 ~ ₺229,99)</span>
  </li><li>
    <strong>故事模式+自由模式合集：</strong><span>₺399,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺299,99</strong>
</b><span>(₺299,99 ~ ₺399,99)</span>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  【Game Introduction】
'Call of Knights' is an RPG card pixel-style game developed by Olive Panda Studio. It is divided into two parts: 'Song of the Knight' and 'Shining Stars,' each offering unique gameplay and content. The game adopts paid download, in-app purchase to unlock model to access all gameplay content.

【In-App Purchases Unlock】
Full Content Unlock: $8.99 USD
Story Mode of Song of the Knight: $4.99 USD
Free Mode of Shining Stars: $4.99 USD
Both modes support experiencing before paying for unlocking. 'Song of the Knight' can be experienced for free until the end of the second chapter, and 'Shining Stars' offers free gameplay for one year. 
Note: The amounts will be converted based on the local exchange rate.

'Song of the Knight':
The story is adapted from the Nobel Prize-winning author Henrik Hien's 'The Knights of the Cross.' The main gameplay involves RPG role-playing with cards, incorporating a partner skill combo system during card battles. Different cards played release exclusive skills, constructing various playstyles. Players will also meet and recruit numerous companions, embarking on an epic journey.

'Shining Stars':
The game is set in a magical continent called Antana, featuring six countries with diverse customs. Players take on the role of a small lord in one of the kingdoms. As the demonic realm is about to invade the continent, players must travel far and wide to find companions for their knightly order, establish their own knightly order, embark on adventures, strengthen their abilities, and defend the human frontlines.

【Device Support】
· iOS 10.0 and above
· Operating memory of 3GB and above
· iPhone 7 and above
· iPad Air 3 and above

【Contact Us】
If you need assistance during the game or encounter issues, feel free to contact us via email.
Official Email: knight@longyougame.com
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/51/db/4a/51db4a80-9482-7bee-95db-3144b2684696/14ccc6a9-ec79-4c52-b7e8-e04a6d586069_5.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/31/42/ba/3142babe-2deb-0179-5109-8b3488a828a8/cf67dc32-c9f7-47be-a5b8-3026962ee8ae_1.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/72/d1/21/72d121d0-9eab-d9a5-330e-70167811ce3c/8523841c-54ad-44d9-87b7-bf3ea99dc712_4.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/53/f2/1b/53f21bc2-c060-95e5-caf9-4bf2ce38e15e/e73c0e5e-9742-4b45-a737-e37d1068515d_2.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/3f/f3/41/3ff3413f-057c-dec8-2a7d-4412f40e2e3e/7a58468a-93f1-4a7c-a73e-9e292d197020_3.png/406x228bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/60/36/3b/60363b24-9d7b-8e3b-d443-49830495c878/e1e03def-54a7-4503-9369-9d247b724c74_2732x2048_1.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/ae/10/16/ae101638-f5d5-6166-ec2f-7ca856e276ff/3ac93560-b894-4c71-b4c6-ebfffe6776bd_2732x2048_2.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/f8/f3/78/f8f37853-f7b2-6b7d-2785-68a5612d93cb/92c3d18f-6a63-4283-9187-9c144d5d8e99_2732x2048_3.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/28/c9/3b/28c93b70-53e4-84df-0526-44120b05338b/52a49e67-10bd-401d-b48a-22cf1b703417_2732x2048_4.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/13/44/0f/13440f68-d80b-373d-7994-4efb29d892f0/365fcda9-011a-4cba-8714-dfe43a83d063_2732x2048_5.png/552x414bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>