<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2024-12-12T00:12:25.801Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T00:12:25.803Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juice Watch]]></title>
        <id>Juice Watch-1733962140079</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/juice-watch/id1485101937?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T00:09:00.079Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺299,99 → ₺39,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/juice-watch/id1485101937?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/9a/15/8c/9a158cb2-95af-1749-57dd-7b9c90786533/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺299,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺39,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Monitor your iPhone battery level from your wrist.

Juice Watch is a simple app designed to do two things well:

• Show the battery level of the paired iPhone in a complication on Apple Watch

• Deliver a notification on your iPhone when your Apple Watch is charging and gets above 90% (or whatever level you choose, from 50% to 100%)

Just glance at your wrist to monitor the charge of your iPhone throughout the day. Or, keep tabs on the battery level of your iPhone while it is plugged in and charging in another room.

You can see both your iPhone and Apple Watch battery levels on the same complication.

You can also get a notification on your Apple Watch when the paired iPhone is charging and reaches at least 80% (or whatever level you choose, from 50% to 100%).

You can set up low battery notifications, to get notifications when your Apple Watch or iPhone battery is low.

Juice Watch is available for a wide variety of complications, so you can use it on your favorite watch faces.

You can also use this app to check your Apple Watch battery level from your paired iPhone. This can be useful while your Apple Watch is charging somewhere else.

Keep in mind that the iPhone battery level shown on Apple Watch is not real-time. It is refreshed periodically, about every 5–60 minutes. The Apple Watch battery level shown on the paired iPhone refreshes at approximately the same rate.

As of iOS 17 and watchOS 10, Juice Watch reports battery levels rounded to the nearest 5% since that's now the granularity that Apple makes available to apps.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/e7/79/05/e77905fd-8531-93f9-7e63-b31ba9d738fd/85dc5c23-12a5-430e-be68-dbbb2066cdfa_5.5_inch_-_1_-_en.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/f6/e1/e5/f6e1e581-ac55-46a4-6a3d-eeabe3789c9f/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/a2/b1/d9/a2b1d958-8649-bd40-7c70-9de4cc49a09a/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threema. The Secure Messenger]]></title>
        <id>Threema. The Secure Messenger-1733962140079</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/threema-the-secure-messenger/id578665578?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T00:09:00.079Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺249,99 → ₺129,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/threema-the-secure-messenger/id578665578?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/7c/19/41/7c1941ce-eaba-ce93-bfb4-894718fdb412/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007epad-0-0-0-1-0-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺249,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺129,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Threema is the world’s best-selling secure messenger and keeps your data out of the hands of hackers, corporations, and governments. The service can be used completely anonymously. Threema is open source and offers every feature one would expect from a state-of-the-art instant messenger. The app also allows to make end-to-end encrypted voice, video and group calls. Using the desktop app and the web client, you can also use Threema from your desktop.

PRIVACY AND ANONYMITY
Threema is designed from the ground up to generate as little data on servers as possible. Group memberships and contact lists are managed on your device only, and never stored on our servers. Messages are immediately deleted after they have been delivered. Local files are stored encrypted on your mobile phone or tablet. All this effectively prevents the collection and misuse of your personal information, including metadata. Threema is fully compliant with the European privacy legislation (GDPR).

ROCK-SOLID ENCRYPTION
Threema end-to-end encrypts all your communication, including messages, voice and video calls, group chats, files, and even status messages. Only the intended recipient, and nobody else, can read your messages. Threema uses the trusted open source NaCl cryptography library for encryption. The encryption keys are generated and safely stored on the users’ devices to prevent backdoor access or copies.

COMPREHENSIVE FEATURES 
Threema is not only an encrypted and private messenger but also versatile and feature-rich.

• Write text and send voice messages
• Edit and delete sent messages on the recipient’s end
• Make voice, video and group calls
• Share videos, pictures and locations
• Send any type of file (PDF, animated GIF, MP3, DOC, ZIP, etc.)
• Use the desktop app or the web client to chat from your computer
• Create groups
• Conduct polls
• Choose between a dark and a light theme
• Quickly and silently reply with the unique agree/disagree feature
• Verify the identity of a contact by scanning their personal QR code
• Use Threema as anonymous instant messaging tool
• Synchronize your contacts (optional)

SERVERS IN SWITZERLAND
All our servers are located in Switzerland, and we develop our software in-house.

FULL ANONYMITY
Each Threema user receives a random Threema ID for identification. A phone number or email address is not required to use Threema. This unique feature allows you to use Threema completely anonymously – no need to give up private information or to open an account. 

OPEN SOURCE AND AUDITS
The source code of the Threema app is open for everyone to review. On top of that, renowned experts are regularly commissioned to conduct systematic security audits of Threema’s code.

NO ADS, NO TRACKERS
Threema is not financed by advertising and does not collect user data.

SUPPORT / CONTACT
For questions or problems please consult our FAQs: https://threema.ch/en/faq
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/a7/9f/a0/a79fa0d4-7034-398e-63f3-687715cb9e15/5721fc4d-3986-4acf-9827-e88688ab0a41_ios-5.5-6.0-en_us-01-promo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/19/d3/d5/19d3d530-8c88-f873-c66f-92dc7ce57122/8acc3dd3-210f-47f5-acd1-2fd01ed3323f_ios-5.5-6.0-en_us-02-promo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/1d/fe/f0/1dfef08f-38c6-8b13-1c2b-8235b9bb9f04/bedeb6f3-3077-4c2d-97ce-ed7decf30982_ios-5.5-6.0-en_us-03-promo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/bb/34/6e/bb346e9b-afab-b9d6-edc5-1cb3cc63abfe/e377e7f9-5ddb-4570-9b2d-a041f8faba58_ios-5.5-6.0-en_us-04-promo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/08/42/ab/0842ab3b-74c3-fe6b-532f-d3cfa9522475/f2796251-8683-4bc4-84ef-97dd1e3311a5_ios-5.5-6.0-en_us-05-promo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/6a/ad/2a/6aad2a3b-468a-7b06-6f27-1a7198a70e56/5e3a0736-c922-4984-89f6-c018d3153571_ios-5.5-6.0-en_us-06-promo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/a8/c6/ab/a8c6ab68-083c-1bc0-a7ab-270f598ffe6f/0dc39346-e7d7-4c6c-8fdd-15d279f8d14b_ios-5.5-6.0-en_us-07-promo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/b5/37/aa/b537aa01-6e81-f7b0-6229-70d607362ead/f9278ae6-f356-43c6-a876-d92d94635316_ios-5.5-6.0-en_us-08-promo.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/4b/d1/dd/4bd1dd4a-eb32-fe5b-a42f-124274b60534/533279dd-6c3b-4a59-bf54-a8622e8510a6_ios-i_pad_3-6.0-en_us-01-promo.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/dd/b2/e7/ddb2e7d7-308e-1f40-3ba1-4c3de550c079/a440ea5c-bf56-460c-9389-8e3d60edb925_ios-i_pad_3-6.0-en_us-03-promo.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/26/8a/8e/268a8e0c-b00b-fb50-0e7b-436dfbbcddd5/1444d332-a60c-45fd-8f60-71210358bd7e_ios-i_pad_3-6.0-en_us-04-promo.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/02/c4/72/02c472af-ade8-7bb0-2515-be2708fe42c3/79a693f4-176a-42fa-80ff-eef0a42cca1b_ios-i_pad_3-6.0-en_us-05-promo.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/b3/f5/1a/b3f51a19-cc7e-624e-d1a8-3151a73b35e6/70630c12-a929-46a3-aedc-18cefaf87801_ios-i_pad_3-6.0-en_us-06-promo.png/552x414bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>