<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2024-12-03T00:13:24.993Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T00:13:24.994Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MovieSpirit - Movie Maker Pro]]></title>
        <id>MovieSpirit - Movie Maker Pro-1733184601959</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/moviespirit-movie-maker-pro/id1020541183?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T00:10:01.959Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺449,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/moviespirit-movie-maker-pro/id1020541183?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/58/aa/8f/58aa8fc3-3ede-5036-6576-4f920c5138f3/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-0-0-7-0-0-sRGB-0-0-0-GLES2_U002c0-512MB-85-220-0-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺449,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Pay once, use forever！ You are free to use and upgrade the App in your whole life once you pay for the download once.

Do you want to share your exciting and memorable moments with someone?
Do you want to make your own movie?
Do you want to be a director, a producer, a starring actor?

In MovieSpirit, these characters can all be done by you alone!

With MovieSpirit, you can combine various media materials, such as videos, photos, music, text, recording and finger graffiti, and according to your creativity,  edit them together and add various special effects (scene switching effects, Text animation, Filter effects, video Intro, masks and so on) to create your own movie. 

Main functions:

- Crop, split, merge, cut, transform, flip and scale media clips
- Overlay multi-layers video (Picture-in-picture effect),  no limit to the number of videos or pictures
- Professional Video Ratio, Scalable Timeline (frame by frame), Unlimited Track Layers
- Add masks (Line mask, Rectangle mask, Circle mask, Text mask and Path mask options) to hide or show parts of the video
- Video matting, remove video background
- Cutout Tool (Custom Shape Tools such as Pen Tool, Lasso Tool, Smudge Tool and Text Tool can be used for image matting)
- Replace background for green/blue screen video, chroma key compositing
- up to 50 special effects options, such as Blur, Snow, Rain, Bubble, Flower, Earthquake, Mirror, Fireworks, Smoke, Vortex, flame, Starry Sky and so on
- Gradual Opaque
- Fast-Forward, Slow-Motion and reverse video (1/12 Slow to 16-fold Speed)
- Text-to-Voice function (dozens of language options)
- 360 Degrees rotating video
- Multiple Image Blending modes
- Various fonts, text templates, text colors, vertical text, emojis, shadows, text strokes, alignment etc., supports downloading new fonts from Internet or icloud 
- Built-in free music and sound effects in various styles, adding music from your computer or from iTunes, and extracting audio from videos
- Voice recording
- Draw graffiti with your finger directly on the film, variety of auxiliary drawing shape tools that can be freely selected such as straight line, curve, arrow, circle, square, triangle, star, heart, colorful text and so on
- Simple automatic tracking function
- Add movable mosaic
- Custom Background Color, such as solid color, gradient color and extract color from picture
- Dozens of Animation effects
- Adjustable Brightness, Contrast, Saturation, Exposure, White Balance, Gamma
- Create your own GIF animation
- Private Custom Intro titles (sold separately)
- Up to 80 filter effects (sketch, comics, fisheye, magnifiers, glass, background blur, rotation blur, vortex, various color filter and so on
- Up to 60 scene switching effects
- dozens of appearance shapes can be set for video/picture such as circle, heart, diamond, star, various irregular shapes and even customize unique shapes
- Can turn the video/photo into black and white, highlight the part that needs to be highlighted (Color Splash)
- Free to deform video/photo into irregular shapes
- Add motion points to video/photo/text to make them move, zoom, rotate and move together to create a variety of gorgeous effects, such as fade-in and fade-out effect and up to 100 multiple phantom effect
- Real-time preview, high resolution video output (HD)
- Import multimedia material directly from your computer via Wi-Fi: videos, photos, music and GIF animations
- Save and share videos directly to social networks such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, iCloud, WeChat, Mailbox and so on
- Helpful video tutorials


We're looking forward to any feedback and comments on MovieSpirit, and if you have any query or problem, please feel free to contact us via email verytools2006@gmail.com

We are committed to your long-term satisfaction. Thanks!
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/84/43/c6/8443c612-e66f-2cc4-5404-28496758665d/mzl.vouvntxp.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/81/a6/b9/81a6b968-db10-16b0-7122-fc4bf9a89139/mzl.irrolmav.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/5e/8d/10/5e8d104d-5b8e-8725-b913-0fec3a00d852/mzl.mhpnjkrz.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/55/22/99/552299e2-cf56-fa58-c350-3896ade7ec99/mzl.tasdcgmo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/e5/55/80/e55580c3-ea91-dee0-2e79-6aacfa44eaa6/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/d1/a0/dd/d1a0dd33-42a6-43d9-bd74-e4d1aaf3e727/mzl.gyaqzhtx.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/14/f8/b1/14f8b185-87f3-3d82-6b0c-e34173307848/mzl.zegpdavb.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/f2/8a/dd/f28addfb-74f5-1398-1267-8fb1cabff9e6/mzl.spbtrnit.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/5f/3d/f1/5f3df1c1-daac-1cb8-f8c2-adf671519289/mzl.rkeuxqiq.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/b8/15/b1/b815b16e-b741-2fb6-68f7-7f1a61ac89b5/pr_source.jpg/576x768bb.jpg" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phone Drive: File Storage Sync]]></title>
        <id>Phone Drive: File Storage Sync-1733184601959</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/phone-drive-file-storage-sync/id431033044?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T00:10:01.959Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺179,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/phone-drive-file-storage-sync/id431033044?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/c9/cc/63/c9cc6306-92d8-14c0-5bfb-1c1289c4bf07/AppIcon-pro-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺179,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Introducing Phone Drive - File Manager: Transform your iOS device into a portable Wireless Flash Drive.

With Phone Drive, you can effortlessly store, view, and manage local or cloud files on your iPhone or iPad. Seamlessly connect to Phone Drive from any Mac or PC over a WiFi network and transfer files through simple drag and drop from Web Browser, Finder or Windows Explorer.

Experience the convenience of managing multiple cloud accounts in a single application. Download, upload, view, and even stream videos or music directly from your cloud drives.

Phone Drive boasts a comprehensive set of features including a document viewer, PDF reader, music player, image viewer, voice recorder, text editor, file manager, and support for various file operations such as delete, move, copy, email, share, zip, unzip, and more.


*** KEY FEATURES ***
• SUPPORT CLOUD STORAGE: 
Connect to multiple Dropbox, OneDrive, Box Drive, FTP, WebDAV, Yandex Disk, and iCloud Drive storage accounts. (*additional in-app purchase required)

• MULTIMEDIA PLAYER:
Create custom audio playlists with options like repeat, shuffle, background playback, and multitask remote control. Stream videos and music directly from your cloud storage.

• DOCUMENT READER:
View MS Office, iWork, Text, and HTML files with ease.

• FILE OPERATION:
Effortlessly move, copy, rename, delete, zip, unzip, unrar, create files, and folders.

• FILE SHARING:
Share files with other iPhone/iPad devices via Bluetooth or Wi-Fi, with automatic search for nearby available devices.

• EASY FILE UPLOAD:
Conveniently upload files through drag and drop via your PC/Mac web browser or USB using iTunes.

• TEXT EDITOR:
Edit text files and source codes directly on your iOS device with the built-in text editor.

• IMPORT/ FILES CREATION:
Create text files, capture images, record videos or voice memos, and import pictures from your photo library.

• ﻿PASSCODE LOCK:
Protect your files from unauthorized access. Utilize Touch ID and Face ID support for secure unlocking.

• UNIVERSALITY:
Enjoy the benefits of this app on both iPhone and iPad with a single purchase.


*** AUDIO PLAYER ***
• Play MP3 files as playlists.
• Repeat and shuffle songs.
• Background audio playback.
• Multitask audio remote control.
• Stream music from cloud storage.


*** VIEWABLE FORMATS ***
Phone Drive supports the following formats:

• Audio (WAV, MP3, M4A, CAF, AIF, AIFF, AAC)
• Images (JPG, PNG, GIF, BMP, TIF, TIFF, ICO)
• Movies (MP4, MOV, MPV, M4V)
• iWorks (Pages, numbers, and Keynote)
• Microsoft Office (Word, Excel and PowerPoint)
• RTF (Rich Text Format)
• RTFD (TextEdit with embedded images)
• PDF Documents
• Plain text
• Source code
• HTML web pages 
• Web archives


Explore more about Phone Drive at:
Website : https://sixbytes.io
Twitter: https://twitter.com/SixbytesApp
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/sixbytesapp

For detailed information, please review our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy:
• Terms of service: https://sixbytes.io/assets/terms-of-service.pdf
• Privacy policy: https://sixbytes.io/assets/privacy-policy.pdf
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/cf/c0/2c/cfc02c35-bf45-a827-7ca0-b2c03f6b69b8/90e9cb2e-c1b3-475c-8571-ceaa09767197_3.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/f4/09/a8/f409a8b4-6260-238e-4046-9adbc29f09f6/8ddeb87c-1c5e-4418-964f-d78502087947_2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/df/eb/7f/dfeb7fd7-c996-afc4-d23a-14aebab407fd/11a30081-599f-4f3c-8009-a3874b91b82b_3.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/5d/86/fb/5d86fb8c-63a6-1a76-a598-b1641d393011/6c76e2c2-4cfe-43a3-963d-4b066a6358e7_4.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/c5/55/2c/c5552ccc-c6c7-3e98-14b1-7042d4808ffb/b5b281fb-7ed7-4bc6-ab54-2c743aa7e14b_5.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/36/8d/eb/368deb50-321c-42ea-9ddf-5bb9496cc519/6f843c4e-18c1-4c53-8f38-a7a1543fd104_5.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/d4/65/f1/d465f168-85ca-82f8-ec0f-0c557db09e04/3254e269-f02d-4cd6-9664-52089985f87f_4.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/f9/65/fe/f965feef-1794-d41b-3d6e-1487a3b60e49/451646c9-7bf7-4d67-a07b-c249a7127e4f_2.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/f3/08/e2/f308e201-bfd2-a2ed-562d-c50aa39c73f6/8c314339-0a7a-4e8b-947a-b48fc8292397_3.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/ad/ea/a4/adeaa4c0-a7de-00e2-0849-74f83aff32d2/acf4455a-fb73-4b74-87b5-f57865726da3_4.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/3f/5d/a4/3f5da4bc-6c51-00ab-1f82-cae5da85cbf0/072d7521-1f9c-4a38-b3bb-8df84b05c38a_5.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/62/f4/56/62f45630-d0b9-d945-d9e2-97411bd985a5/49f59f36-9362-4554-8b82-a05a90e2ee86_5.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timeline - World history]]></title>
        <id>Timeline - World history-1733184601959</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/timeline-world-history/id818394449?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T00:10:01.959Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺179,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/timeline-world-history/id818394449?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/b7/a6/ec/b7a6ec8f-0fe7-2917-0aaf-237ee83bb763/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-0-0-7-0-0-sRGB-0-0-0-GLES2_U002c0-512MB-85-220-0-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺179,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  A world timeline app that show important world event to you.
after play game or watch tv, get some time to find what happened in the real world，maybe you will find something different.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/ef/7d/81/ef7d8191-f4b2-5fb3-f540-72e2abca130f/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/f0/89/30/f08930c6-daf1-b099-f634-49948acb789c/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/10/44/ca/1044cae5-017c-edfc-986f-c29f7a854c27/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/e8/9d/85/e89d85e1-e9a2-3df7-02a5-8c1f8d5b942f/mzl.fjxnqyjj.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/5f/72/42/5f7242ad-b942-e8f1-ff92-a4c52453dd19/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/e5/fe/18/e5fe182d-8252-4d52-3191-e68ccd9f84c8/pr_source.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/c9/76/f0/c976f06d-17f1-abc2-c4d4-c6fb87b58b14/mzl.xgzaumpc.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/53/c2/5f/53c25feb-0325-c3b0-8997-cc731afed597/pr_source.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RAIN RADAR ° live weather maps]]></title>
        <id>RAIN RADAR ° live weather maps-1733184601959</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/rain-radar-live-weather-maps/id488674899?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T00:10:01.959Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺599,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/rain-radar-live-weather-maps/id488674899?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/44/a6/eb/44a6ebc2-0045-22bb-5c81-8cbfcc93bfb0/AppIcon-Full-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺599,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Imagine that the entire globe is at your fingertips. Never before has getting weather information been as exciting and interactive as it is in the “Weather Now” application.
Amazingly beautiful 3D images of our planet draws your attention for so long that you may forget that the application has other useful features that allows you easy access to precise, global weather information.

The main features of “Weather Now” are the “home screen” and the forecast page with a unique way of scaling the charts. On the “home screen”, you can get information on the selected location such as local time and current weather with detailed weather conditions, and, of course, an incredibly beautiful three-dimensional image of the globe with realistic-looking atmosphere, the sun and the stars. You can manually turn it, increase and decrease its size, run the slow spinning animation or stop it. Installed in a cradle or dock station, the application can run as a screensaver, attracting your friends and fellows.

The weather forecast is provided by CustomWeather, Inc, an American weather provider of global weather information for over 11 years. CustomWeather is a leader in technology and meteorological innovation, providing local weather information to companies and application developers around the world.

The current weather data is gathered from thousands of professionally installed and maintained weather stations installed mostly at airports. WeatherNow only shows current weather from stations that have reported local weather conditions within the past hour. Current weather data is refreshed every 30 minutes; that is twice as frequent as most other weather providers can offer. Unique 48-hour forecasts from over 80,000 locations around the world provide a level of coverage and detail that simply cannot be found elsewhere.

Current weather information includes: description, air temperature, wind direction and force, humidity, dew point, pressure, visibility, as well as comfort index with reference to current weather conditions. 
Detailed weather forecast information includes: description, day and night air temperature, wind direction and force, humidity, UV index, probability of precipitation, and comfort index with reference to current weather conditions.

Features:
• Chic 3D “home screen” with high-quality real-time image of the earth, atmosphere, the stars and the sun 
• Weather Maps, include: Clouds Cover, Precipitation's, Pressure, Wind and Temperature
• Current temperature on the icon badge
• Easily select different cities using the city carousel with national flags 
• 15-day forecast chart with detailed daily weather conditions, independent day and night temperature charts 
• 48-hour hourly forecast with detailed information with real-time changing of chart step
• Database of 80 000 cities with weather information, quick look-up and automatic detection of location
• Extended application setting for best application experience
• Current time and date for selected location
• Sunrise and sunset time, UI Index
• Multi Language support
• Share weather info use your Twitter account
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/a3/3d/2a/a33d2a55-48a0-198c-5b98-6f1dd4cb2126/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/16/b2/96/16b296cb-a323-c26c-1c67-8d336eaade89/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/72/37/90/723790d9-642f-995f-5469-1e588dc81498/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/0d/3f/2d/0d3f2de0-3a41-ebad-bb58-e53b811f4c3d/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/5c/1b/62/5c1b625d-5f1f-e349-1560-7c82a12cf0fe/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/9d/59/61/9d596154-9d65-80c9-ab53-83ffd40e6ef8/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/df/13/66/df13660d-b292-b476-d9e2-e0b2e010d0ba/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/43/88/9c/43889c88-ab93-e998-d855-c08f4fb805db/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/0d/72/7c/0d727cce-b561-e9d2-a7db-3a3de3baa490/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/a3/c4/ea/a3c4ead7-014d-f4c2-af52-4e2eecd97377/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/c7/3b/f1/c73bf143-8967-2204-b939-40b74f669980/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/17/0f/e4/170fe4c4-a239-274a-d507-99efff510706/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>