<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2024-11-24T12:07:23.653Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T12:07:23.653Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things 3]]></title>
        <id>Things 3-1732449836211</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/things-3/id904237743?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T12:03:56.211Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺399,99 → ₺249,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/things-3/id904237743?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/fb/bb/6a/fbbb6a0a-23f8-fc49-4552-50a6b40b8123/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007ephone-0-1-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺399,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺249,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Get things done! The award-winning Things app helps you plan your day, manage your projects, and make real progress toward your goals.

Best of all, it’s easy to use. Within the hour, you’ll have everything off your mind and neatly organized—from routine tasks to your biggest life goals—and you can start focusing on what matters today.

“Things offers the best combination of design and functionality of any app we tested, with nearly all the features of other power user applications and a delightful interface that never gets in the way of your work.”
—Wirecutter, The New York Times


KEY FEATURES

• Your To-Dos
Your basic building block is the almighty To-Do—each a small step toward a great accomplishment. You can add notes, tag it, schedule it, and break it down into smaller steps.

• Your Projects
Create a Project for any big goal, then add the to-dos to reach it. Use headings to structure your list as you outline your plan. There’s also a place to jot down your notes, and a deadline to keep you on schedule.

• Your Areas
Create an Area for each sphere of your life, such as Work, Family, Finance, and so on. This keeps everything neatly organized, and helps you see the big picture as you set your plans in motion.

• Your Plan
Everything on your schedule is neatly laid out in the Today and Upcoming lists, which show your to-dos and calendar events. Each morning, see what you planned for Today and decide what you want to do. The rest is down to you :)


MORE THINGS TO LOVE

As you dive deeper, you’ll find Things packed with helpful features. Here are just a few:

• Reminders — set a time and Things will remind you.
• Repeaters — automatically repeat to-dos on a schedule you set.
• This Evening — a special place for your evening plans.
• Calendar integration — see your events and to-dos together.
• Tags — categorize your to-dos and quickly filter lists.
• Quick Find — instantly find to-dos or switch between lists.
• Magic Plus — drag the + button to insert to-dos anywhere in a list.
• Share extension — create to-dos with content from other apps.
• Widgets — see lists on your home/lock screens.
• Mail to Things — forward an email to Things; now it’s a to-do.
• Markdown — structure & style your notes.
• And much more!


MADE FOR IPHONE

Things is tailored to the iPhone with deep system integrations as well. A great example is the Share extension, which allows you to create to-dos with content from other apps, such as a link to a website you want to get back to.

You can also enjoy a beautiful dark mode at sunset, connect your calendars, add a variety of widgets, create to-dos via Siri, import from Reminders—Things can do it all! There’s even Shortcuts integration if you want to automate your workflows.


MADE FOR APPLE WATCH

Things comes with a great app for Apple Watch. Just raise your wrist to glance at your Today list, mark to-dos complete as you go, and dictate new ones on the fly—all synced instantly with your iPhone, iPad, and Mac.


AWARD-WINNING DESIGN

Made in Stuttgart, with two Apple Design Awards to its name, Things is a fine example of German engineering: designed not only to look fantastic, but to be perfectly functional as well. Every detail is thoughtfully considered, then polished to perfection.

“It’s like the unicorn of productivity tools: deep enough for serious work, surprisingly easy to use, and gorgeous enough to enjoy staring at.”
—Apple


GET THINGS TODAY

Whatever it is you want to accomplish in life, Things can help you get there. Install the app today and see what you can do!

• Things is also available for Mac, iPad, and Apple Vision Pro (sold separately).
• Sync is provided for free via our Things Cloud service.
• A free trial is available for Mac: www.things.app

If you have any questions, please get in touch. We provide professional support and will be glad to help you!
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/9b/3f/fb/9b3ffb80-8088-4b48-cd18-7c3d631e0ec6/6d2e1e37-b053-4cc7-b887-2d7b25fc9222_iPhone_8_Plus_-_1.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/61/aa/28/61aa281c-b27d-8857-7cdb-6d1eb6b8e6ef/2b726649-1d6e-4360-8e80-aa96ea4f7e48_iPhone_8_Plus_-_2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/b4/1a/14/b41a1441-896b-b593-4809-fcb5c987e6bd/10f6325d-b427-41e8-a227-04168f3ddc02_iPhone_8_Plus_-_3.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/10/76/b8/1076b8d6-be56-6f34-9b42-3f67c24b6ff3/c1b6c31b-50e0-48de-ad8e-1e48446ddc15_iPhone_8_Plus_-_4.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/7e/d9/4f/7ed94fb2-f101-d2e3-9b56-a6e66528a4e5/487b250b-431c-4659-9e9a-361c6c79b1e0_iPhone_8_Plus_-_5.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/d9/06/8f/d9068fa7-c157-d6fc-7586-a9a2bc18f9dc/f2a118b6-9811-4a1b-bec5-cc0b0bc677eb_iPhone_8_Plus_-_6.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>