<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-04-13T17:05:20.340Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:99063474310237184) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:99063474310237184+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T17:05:20.340Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deflection]]></title>
        <id>Deflection-1744563731769</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/deflection/id670400597?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-13T17:02:11.769Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺449,99 → ₺229,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/deflection/id670400597?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/63/ca/0b/63ca0b9f-d0f0-41b2-e454-3186c4e2691d/AppIcons-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺449,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺229,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Deflection is a powerful, versatile calculator for beams, 2D trusses, and 2D frames.  The interface is simple and intuitive, and the graphical output is state-of-the-art.  In addition to reaction, shear, bending moment, and deflection results, Deflection also computes internal shear and bending stress along the cross section and along the beam.

2D FRAME AND TRUSS EDITOR

The 2D editor is seamlessly integrated with the beam editor.  Draw arbitrary frame and truss structures and apply loads and constraints using the same simple interface as for beams.  You can visualize results directly within the 2D editor, or you can select a beam and get additional insights. 

INTERNAL STRESSES

Obtain internal bending and shear stress diagrams in addition to shear, bending, and deflection diagrams.  The internal stresses can be visualized along the length of the beam as well as along the vertical axis of the cross section using the beam editor.

CROSS SECTION EDITOR

Edit built-in cross sections.  Moment of inertia and area values are automatically calculated and applied to the rest of the beam calculations.

MORE FEATURES

• The built-in database contains more data for your reference and convenience.
• Apply beam self-weight optionally
• Unlimited design files
• Quick-start templates

CONTACT

We like to hear from you!  Please email contact@ketchep.com if you have any issues, questions, or comments.
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>