<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-04-24T15:18:10.731Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:99063474310237184) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:99063474310237184+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T15:18:10.731Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TuneShift]]></title>
        <id>TuneShift-1745506952822</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/tuneshift/id6739975257?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T15:02:32.822Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺179,99 → ₺129,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/tuneshift/id6739975257?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/d2/71/73/d27173c4-c912-d68d-3ec2-1ecb801c01d5/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007ephone-0-1-0-85-220.jpeg/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺179,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺129,99</strong>
</b><span>(₺129,99 ~ ₺179,99)</span>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  TuneShift is the ultimate music playlist migration tool that seamlessly transfers your favorite tracks from Spotify and YouTube Music to Apple Music in seconds.
﻿
Tired of manually recreating your carefully curated playlists? TuneShift solves this problem with just a few taps. Our intelligent matching system ensures your music collection transitions smoothly between platforms with maximum accuracy.
﻿
KEY FEATURES:
• One-tap playlist migration from Spotify and YouTube Music to Apple Music
• Smart track matching to find the closest versions of your songs
• Preserves your original playlist organization and order
• Track migration progress in real-time
• Clean, intuitive interface designed for music lovers
﻿
TuneShift respects your privacy. We only access your playlists with your permission and never store your login credentials.
﻿
Whether you're switching music services or just want to maintain libraries across multiple platforms, TuneShift makes the process quick and painless.
﻿
Download TuneShift now and take your music everywhere you go!
﻿
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>