<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-04-30T16:21:09.245Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:99063474310237184) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:99063474310237184+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:21:09.245Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hero's Adventure]]></title>
        <id>Hero's Adventure-1746028957031</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/heros-adventure/id6711347049?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:02:37.031Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺299,99 → ₺249,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/heros-adventure/id6711347049?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/8d/40/ca/8d40ca27-bab9-da59-670a-86064b73d1ff/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺299,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺249,99</strong>
</b><span>(₺249,99 ~ ₺299,99)</span>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Hero's Adventure is an open-world Wuxia RPG developed by Half Amateur Studio.You will commence your journey as an underdog in the tumultuous Martial World and will be met with a wide array of choices as you navigate your own heroic saga.

Game Features

[Unexpected Encounters Await]
Throughout your journey, you will run into scripted and unexpected encounters. Perhaps you'll cross paths with an ambitious lieutenant amidst a power struggle at a humble inn, or you’ll run into a retired kung fu master in a nameless village. These will be the experiences you will learn to expect in the ever-changing Jianghu.

Beware, each encounter might associate and change your relationship with the 30+ factions involved in the power struggle in this chaotic Martial World. And remember: every choice you make, every person you befriend (or offend), and every faction you engage will leave a mark.

[Become the Master of Martial Arts]
Whether you're decoding ancient techniques off a forgotten scroll, or prefer training with a battle-hardened warrior, there’s no correct solution for mastering martial arts. Choose from a variety of weapon types and explore 300+ martial arts skills, the Jianghu will be yours to conquer.

[Explore a Living, Breathing World]
In this Wuxia simulator, you'll get to explore 80 cities and villages that bring wuxia to life. Witness how villagers go about their daily routines, and experience the rhythms of ancient Chinese cities.

[Craft Your Narrative]
To provide an experience where you can embody your own martial spirit, Hero’s Adventure has over 10 distinct endings. Whether you choose to be a noble swordsman, a guardian of the nation, or an agent of chaos, you'll find an ending that aligns with your chosen path in Hero's Adventure.

Discord: https://discord.gg/bcX8pry8ZV
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>