<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-03-12T23:05:21.479Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T23:05:21.480Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kingdom Rush Frontiers TD]]></title>
        <id>Kingdom Rush Frontiers TD-1741820532482</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/kingdom-rush-frontiers-td/id598581396?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T23:02:12.482Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺99,99 → ₺39,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/kingdom-rush-frontiers-td/id598581396?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/ec/04/70/ec0470a6-3e3b-9fba-453e-30a34ddc6b81/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-5-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺99,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺39,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Kingdom Rush Frontiers is a whole new level of the furiously fast, enchantingly charming gameplay that made kingdom Rush an award-winning Tower Defense hit.
Defend exotic lands from dragons, man-eating plants, and ghastly denizens of the underworld -all with flashy towers, levels, heroes, and more goodies to help you crush your enemies to a pulp.

BUILD MIGHTY TOWERS!
• OVER 18 TOWER ABILITIES! Unleash Death Riders, pestilence clouds, or assassins that steal and kill your enemies!
• 8 SPECIALIZED TOWER UPGRADES! Slice, sizzle, and stomp your foes with Crossbow Forts, Mighty Templars, Necromancers, and even Earthquake Machines - hey, we told you we were shaking things up.
• UPGRADE SYSTEM allows you to min/max your towers towards your preferred strategy.
• Fortify the frontier in exotic new lands - hold the line in deserts, jungles, and even the underworld!

TRAIN LEGENDARY HEROES
• 16 LEGENDARY HEROES. Choose among mighty champions and train their abilities! Each has unique specialties that fit different play styles and strategies!
• Special units and features on every stage! Watch out for the Black Dragon!

DEFEAT THEM ALL
• OVER 40 ENEMIES with unique abilities! Stay on your toes as you fight through desert sandworms, tribal shamans, nomad tribes, and underground terrors. Action like you have never seen before!
• MERCILESS BOSS FIGHTS! Hey, we told you to get those upgrades...

MORE MIND-BOGGLING CONTENT
• Hours of gameplay with OVER 80 ACHIEVEMENTS! what can you expect from Ironhide Games, the creators of Kingdom rush? You will be hooked for hours searching for Easter eggs and achievements!
• IN-GAME ENCYCLOPEDIA! learn all about your enemies and you will be able to plan the best strategy to defeat them. Study up!
• CLASSIC, IRON, AND HEROIC GAME MODES to challenge your tactical skills!
• 3 DIFFICULTY MODES! Are you up for a real challenge? Go with Hard mode!
• PLAY IT OFFLINE! No internet? No problem! You will be able to jump into real action even offline!

-----------------------------------------------------

PRAISE FOR KINGDOM RUSH: IGN Editor's Choice, Slide To Play Must Have, 148 Apps Editor's Choice, Jay is Games Game of the Year, Pocket Gamer Gold Award, Touch Arcade 4.5/5

Terms and Conditions:
https://www.ironhidegames.com/TermsOfService

Privacy Policy:
https://www.ironhidegames.com/PrivacyPolicy

Video creators, podcast creators, and streamers:
We would love to see your content on Youtube and Twitch! We support and promote channel creators so, if you want us to showcase your videos or want to know more about our games, feel free to write to us to contact@ironhidegames.com
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/78/8e/b0/788eb0fc-afa8-245b-799b-a195718790a4/5a6affe9-dc30-420d-a725-ad6aa8e9001b_screenshots_2208x12420001.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/79/98/cd/7998cd5a-99b1-b03b-4c9d-42f9c371611c/10e242a9-64da-43ec-a049-230d6672b48f_screenshots_2208x12420002.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/a0/87/32/a0873242-dd94-fe5d-70f4-ccc55b6d4d54/c1460a05-6fe6-422b-a563-4e245dd8af37_screenshots_2208x12420003.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/9a/ba/96/9aba96b9-f838-936d-0524-c1f932ea79b3/7c12dd14-89b7-41c3-968b-33b7225a8730_screenshots_2208x12420004.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/a3/e1/00/a3e1007a-194c-5dc2-1c97-3c2991b1ab9c/436d4067-8ab6-4f41-9103-69ee4cd85a91_screenshots_2208x12420005.png/406x228bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RAIN RADAR ° live weather maps]]></title>
        <id>RAIN RADAR ° live weather maps-1741820532482</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/rain-radar-live-weather-maps/id488674899?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T23:02:12.482Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺599,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/rain-radar-live-weather-maps/id488674899?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/44/a6/eb/44a6ebc2-0045-22bb-5c81-8cbfcc93bfb0/AppIcon-Full-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺599,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Imagine that the entire globe is at your fingertips. Never before has getting weather information been as exciting and interactive as it is in the “Weather Now” application.
Amazingly beautiful 3D images of our planet draws your attention for so long that you may forget that the application has other useful features that allows you easy access to precise, global weather information.

The main features of “Weather Now” are the “home screen” and the forecast page with a unique way of scaling the charts. On the “home screen”, you can get information on the selected location such as local time and current weather with detailed weather conditions, and, of course, an incredibly beautiful three-dimensional image of the globe with realistic-looking atmosphere, the sun and the stars. You can manually turn it, increase and decrease its size, run the slow spinning animation or stop it. Installed in a cradle or dock station, the application can run as a screensaver, attracting your friends and fellows.

The weather forecast is provided by CustomWeather, Inc, an American weather provider of global weather information for over 11 years. CustomWeather is a leader in technology and meteorological innovation, providing local weather information to companies and application developers around the world.

The current weather data is gathered from thousands of professionally installed and maintained weather stations installed mostly at airports. WeatherNow only shows current weather from stations that have reported local weather conditions within the past hour. Current weather data is refreshed every 30 minutes; that is twice as frequent as most other weather providers can offer. Unique 48-hour forecasts from over 80,000 locations around the world provide a level of coverage and detail that simply cannot be found elsewhere.

Current weather information includes: description, air temperature, wind direction and force, humidity, dew point, pressure, visibility, as well as comfort index with reference to current weather conditions. 
Detailed weather forecast information includes: description, day and night air temperature, wind direction and force, humidity, UV index, probability of precipitation, and comfort index with reference to current weather conditions.

Features:
• Chic 3D “home screen” with high-quality real-time image of the earth, atmosphere, the stars and the sun 
• Weather Maps, include: Clouds Cover, Precipitation's, Pressure, Wind and Temperature
• Current temperature on the icon badge
• Easily select different cities using the city carousel with national flags 
• 15-day forecast chart with detailed daily weather conditions, independent day and night temperature charts 
• 48-hour hourly forecast with detailed information with real-time changing of chart step
• Database of 80 000 cities with weather information, quick look-up and automatic detection of location
• Extended application setting for best application experience
• Current time and date for selected location
• Sunrise and sunset time, UI Index
• Multi Language support
• Share weather info use your Twitter account
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/a3/3d/2a/a33d2a55-48a0-198c-5b98-6f1dd4cb2126/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/16/b2/96/16b296cb-a323-c26c-1c67-8d336eaade89/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/72/37/90/723790d9-642f-995f-5469-1e588dc81498/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/0d/3f/2d/0d3f2de0-3a41-ebad-bb58-e53b811f4c3d/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/5c/1b/62/5c1b625d-5f1f-e349-1560-7c82a12cf0fe/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/9d/59/61/9d596154-9d65-80c9-ab53-83ffd40e6ef8/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/df/13/66/df13660d-b292-b476-d9e2-e0b2e010d0ba/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/43/88/9c/43889c88-ab93-e998-d855-c08f4fb805db/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/0d/72/7c/0d727cce-b561-e9d2-a7db-3a3de3baa490/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/a3/c4/ea/a3c4ead7-014d-f4c2-af52-4e2eecd97377/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/c7/3b/f1/c73bf143-8967-2204-b939-40b74f669980/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/17/0f/e4/170fe4c4-a239-274a-d507-99efff510706/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>