<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2024-12-26T00:11:21.752Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T00:11:21.753Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stream Music Player]]></title>
        <id>Stream Music Player-1735171683579</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/stream-music-player/id1065802380?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T00:08:03.579Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺99,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/stream-music-player/id1065802380?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/55/32/b3/5532b3ab-619f-3562-24ff-a95ef2c17450/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-0-0-6-0-0-sRGB-0-0-0-GLES2_U002c0-512MB-85-220-0-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺99,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  --- Special release price 50% off! ---

Stream was created to give you a seamless listening, managing and syncing cloud music experience. It allows you to create a personal streaming service with cloud storage like Box, Dropbox, Google Drive, OneDrive and Yandex.Disk to save space on your device and have access to all of your music. 

How it works? 
Upload all music to your favourite cloud storage then use Stream to connect and enjoy your music anywhere.

Add your music to your device without iTunes, easy and fast using local WiFi transfer or download music to your iPhone to play it without internet (Offline mode). It’s a multi-cloud system therefore you can stream lists of music regardless where they are stored.

Access your favourite music across all your devices: iPhone, iPad, iPod library, Box, Dropbox, Google Drive, OneDrive, Yandex.Disk and your computer. Stream your music with in advanced and powerful media player.


Music player:
- Full featured media player
- Sleep timer
- Lock screen playback controls
- Background music playback
- Equalizer with BassBooster
- Over 20 realistic EQ presets
- Stylish audio Visualizer
- Fine scrubbing
- Album cover art

Playlists: 
- Create your own playlists

Media Library: 
- Import music from your iPod library
- Tabs for Songs, Albums, Artists

Manager:
- Wi-Fi Transfer
- Download and upload music, pictures, archives from 
   - Box
   - Dropbox
   - Google Drive
   - OneDrive
   - Yandex.Disk
- Move, rename or delete tracks & songs
- Search by artist, title, album
- Create and manage folders
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/e8/79/98/e87998e8-1a73-d99b-5f75-d4344d0281be/mzl.wlfewzhr.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/8d/b0/2b/8db02bda-d2ea-cd6c-78eb-1f84a5586c1f/mzl.mrxsourg.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/77/2c/91/772c91b0-d4f2-41a5-73bf-9d28d695ed89/mzl.zgltgvov.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/0d/ce/dd/0dceddb8-3044-c9b8-eb69-ada005eaedee/mzl.givnindd.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/63/94/df/6394dfd0-1106-e162-be57-634d68112ee4/mzl.uzkdbrbq.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/f2/7a/44/f27a44f9-3616-949d-a676-6460ce9a3bc0/pr_source.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/ac/60/a6/ac60a691-bc5d-3818-44a1-d59c4ed5015a/pr_source.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/d9/c3/c5/d9c3c5ba-dcd0-080c-11e9-ac16e710f859/pr_source.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/71/78/3a/71783a7a-68da-69da-e32d-d9f95d076338/pr_source.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/95/6a/6f/956a6f8f-2073-8fc9-ec23-ae3321d1a45a/pr_source.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kingdom Rush Frontiers TD]]></title>
        <id>Kingdom Rush Frontiers TD-1735171683579</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/kingdom-rush-frontiers-td/id598581396?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T00:08:03.579Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺99,99 → ₺39,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/kingdom-rush-frontiers-td/id598581396?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/ec/04/70/ec0470a6-3e3b-9fba-453e-30a34ddc6b81/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-5-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺99,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺39,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Kingdom Rush Frontiers is a whole new level of the furiously fast, enchantingly charming gameplay that made kingdom Rush an award-winning Tower Defense hit.
Defend exotic lands from dragons, man-eating plants, and ghastly denizens of the underworld -all with flashy towers, levels, heroes, and more goodies to help you crush your enemies to a pulp.

BUILD MIGHTY TOWERS!
• OVER 18 TOWER ABILITIES! Unleash Death Riders, pestilence clouds, or assassins that steal and kill your enemies!
• 8 SPECIALIZED TOWER UPGRADES! Slice, sizzle, and stomp your foes with Crossbow Forts, Mighty Templars, Necromancers, and even Earthquake Machines - hey, we told you we were shaking things up.
• UPGRADE SYSTEM allows you to min/max your towers towards your preferred strategy.
• Fortify the frontier in exotic new lands - hold the line in deserts, jungles, and even the underworld!

TRAIN LEGENDARY HEROES
• 16 LEGENDARY HEROES. Choose among mighty champions and train their abilities! Each has unique specialties that fit different play styles and strategies!
• Special units and features on every stage! Watch out for the Black Dragon!

DEFEAT THEM ALL
• OVER 40 ENEMIES with unique abilities! Stay on your toes as you fight through desert sandworms, tribal shamans, nomad tribes, and underground terrors. Action like you have never seen before!
• MERCILESS BOSS FIGHTS! Hey, we told you to get those upgrades...

MORE MIND-BOGGLING CONTENT
• Hours of gameplay with OVER 80 ACHIEVEMENTS! what can you expect from Ironhide Games, the creators of Kingdom rush? You will be hooked for hours searching for Easter eggs and achievements!
• IN-GAME ENCYCLOPEDIA! learn all about your enemies and you will be able to plan the best strategy to defeat them. Study up!
• CLASSIC, IRON, AND HEROIC GAME MODES to challenge your tactical skills!
• 3 DIFFICULTY MODES! Are you up for a real challenge? Go with Hard mode!
• PLAY IT OFFLINE! No internet? No problem! You will be able to jump into real action even offline!

-----------------------------------------------------

PRAISE FOR KINGDOM RUSH: IGN Editor's Choice, Slide To Play Must Have, 148 Apps Editor's Choice, Jay is Games Game of the Year, Pocket Gamer Gold Award, Touch Arcade 4.5/5

Terms and Conditions:
https://www.ironhidegames.com/TermsOfService

Privacy Policy:
https://www.ironhidegames.com/PrivacyPolicy

Video creators, podcast creators, and streamers:
We would love to see your content on Youtube and Twitch! We support and promote channel creators so, if you want us to showcase your videos or want to know more about our games, feel free to write to us to contact@ironhidegames.com
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/78/8e/b0/788eb0fc-afa8-245b-799b-a195718790a4/5a6affe9-dc30-420d-a725-ad6aa8e9001b_screenshots_2208x12420001.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/79/98/cd/7998cd5a-99b1-b03b-4c9d-42f9c371611c/10e242a9-64da-43ec-a049-230d6672b48f_screenshots_2208x12420002.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/a0/87/32/a0873242-dd94-fe5d-70f4-ccc55b6d4d54/c1460a05-6fe6-422b-a563-4e245dd8af37_screenshots_2208x12420003.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/9a/ba/96/9aba96b9-f838-936d-0524-c1f932ea79b3/7c12dd14-89b7-41c3-968b-33b7225a8730_screenshots_2208x12420004.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/a3/e1/00/a3e1007a-194c-5dc2-1c97-3c2991b1ab9c/436d4067-8ab6-4f41-9103-69ee4cd85a91_screenshots_2208x12420005.png/406x228bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juice Watch]]></title>
        <id>Juice Watch-1735171683579</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/juice-watch/id1485101937?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T00:08:03.579Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺299,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/juice-watch/id1485101937?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/08/c2/e7/08c2e7c4-33d4-d974-77e7-38ab3c932587/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺299,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Monitor your iPhone battery level from your wrist.

Juice Watch is a simple app designed to do two things well:

• Show the battery level of the paired iPhone in a complication on Apple Watch

• Deliver a notification on your iPhone when your Apple Watch is charging and gets above 90% (or whatever level you choose, from 50% to 100%)

Just glance at your wrist to monitor the charge of your iPhone throughout the day. Or, keep tabs on the battery level of your iPhone while it is plugged in and charging in another room.

You can see both your iPhone and Apple Watch battery levels on the same complication.

You can also get a notification on your Apple Watch when the paired iPhone is charging and reaches at least 80% (or whatever level you choose, from 50% to 100%).

You can set up low battery notifications, to get notifications when your Apple Watch or iPhone battery is low.

Juice Watch is available for a wide variety of complications, so you can use it on your favorite watch faces.

You can also use this app to check your Apple Watch battery level from your paired iPhone. This can be useful while your Apple Watch is charging somewhere else.

Keep in mind that the iPhone battery level shown on Apple Watch is not real-time. It is refreshed periodically, about every 5–60 minutes. The Apple Watch battery level shown on the paired iPhone refreshes at approximately the same rate.

As of iOS 17 and watchOS 10, Juice Watch reports battery levels rounded to the nearest 5% since that's now the granularity that Apple makes available to apps.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/e7/79/05/e77905fd-8531-93f9-7e63-b31ba9d738fd/85dc5c23-12a5-430e-be68-dbbb2066cdfa_5.5_inch_-_1_-_en.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/f6/e1/e5/f6e1e581-ac55-46a4-6a3d-eeabe3789c9f/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/a2/b1/d9/a2b1d958-8649-bd40-7c70-9de4cc49a09a/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>