<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-03-17T13:11:21.149Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:99063474310237184) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:99063474310237184+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T13:11:21.149Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Longshot - Screenshot & OCR]]></title>
        <id>Longshot - Screenshot &amp; OCR-1742216901502</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/longshot-screenshot-ocr/id6450262949?mt=12&amp;uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T13:08:21.502Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pro version lifetime: ₺599,99 → ₺449,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/longshot-screenshot-ocr/id6450262949?mt=12&uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/a0/85/c5/a085c549-adbd-c0e5-ae80-a1c3474ed130/AppIcon-85-220-0-5-0-0-2x-0-0.png/60x60bb.png" />
</a><h2>Discount Information</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Pro version lifetime：</strong><span>₺599,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺449,99</strong>
</b>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  ## Annotation and Color Picking
Conveniently annotate the screen, a great helper for communicating with colleagues, simple and easy to use.

- Drawing tools, shapes, ovals, lines, arrows, text, marker pen, freehand drawing.
- Annotation and measurement, mosaic, blur, annotation notes, measure pixel distances, color picking, rich functions.
- Step annotation, clear expression of ideas, customizable number content
- Convenient operations, shortcuts, undo, save, open, copy to clipboard, easy and simple.

## Scrolling Capture
Optimized image stitching algorithm makes scrolling capture adaptable to various environments, easily capture conversation context scrolling up and down.

- Vertical/horizontal/360 degrees, support vertical, horizontal, panoramic scrolling capture, scroll any direction to capture.
- Non-solid color background/non-scrolling areas, capture area can include non-scrolling objects with non-solid color background, good scrolling capture screenshot stitching.
- Dynamically adjust scrolling direction/area, can change scrolling direction and readjust capture area after completion for restitching during scrolling.
- Entire window scrolling capture, hold Option to capture entire scrolling window screenshot, automatic edge area handling.

## OCR Text Recognition
Offline OCR algorithm with emphasis on privacy protection. Quickly extract text from images, videos, documents or anywhere.

- Select screen area, recognize text, copy to clipboard, paste to notes, editors, messages etc.
- Support QR and barcode recognition, quickly open corresponding links.
- Support text-to-speech playback of recognized text.

## Screen Element Measurement
Quickly measure any content on screen, automatically recognize distances and element sizes.

- Measure distance, automatically recognize distance between elements or objects on screen, annotate distance.
- Measure element, just select approximate element area, can automatically snap to element and annotate size.
- Support distance and element edge color tolerance adjustment for more precise localization.

## Image Pinning
Turn images, text from anywhere into desktop pins for convenient comparison.

- Clipboard pinning, pin images, text, HTML etc. from clipboard to desktop.
- Double-click pinned image, double-click pinned image or open pinned image on desktop to view.
- Pinned image scrolling, scroll pinned image, double-click to close or minimize, support flipping and mirroring etc image operations.

## Screen Recording
Quickly record steps, one click to record full screen, selected area or window for easy sharing.

- Support full-screen, region and window recording, application recording.
- Support system sound, microphone recording, frame rate settings etc.

## Window Capture
Select window to highlight subject, make capture area better convey intent.

- Intelligent window recognition, automatically highlight window mouse is in.
- Multiple window combinations, hold Shift to select multiple windows for combined capture.

## Contact
Full introduction: https://longshot.chitaner.com
Email: office.chitaner@gmail.com
QQ group: 780402788

## Purchase
Lifetime license of Longshot Pro allows unlimited screenshot scrolling, step annotation, element measurement and sizing annotation, OCR text recognition, custom hotkeys - unlock all current pro features.

-------------------------------------------------------
Privacy Policy: https://longshot.chitaner.com/privacy/
Terms of Use: https://longshot.chitaner.com/terms/
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/4e/71/1b/4e711bdc-3773-cd52-d49f-b122d2b58d08/en_page_1.jpg/800x500bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/c6/9f/e1/c69fe102-71d6-1041-77ff-5826371c0cc5/en_page_2.jpg/800x500bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/41/48/aa/4148aa0d-72c4-3897-31ff-83d421d8b53f/en_page_3.jpg/800x500bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/c4/12/84/c4128495-b08a-f436-58aa-2ab52d0117d1/en_page_4.jpg/800x500bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/7d/d6/b1/7dd6b183-8a04-4762-1b49-e1a645bcd1f5/en_page_5.jpg/800x500bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/c7/9d/54/c79d5475-668c-fd73-f2ec-f9daec3c78ee/en_page_6.jpg/800x500bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/4c/e4/30/4ce4305c-a706-c41a-c34b-ba664a8f2128/en_page_7.jpg/800x500bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/a3/b2/46/a3b246bc-7960-59d2-f690-7fe27d8f97fa/en_page_8.jpg/800x500bb.jpg" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>