<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2025-04-09T14:06:18.689Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:49753370488353792) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:49753370488353792+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T14:06:18.689Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iSleeper: Sleep Tracker]]></title>
        <id>iSleeper: Sleep Tracker-1744207375612</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/isleeper-sleep-tracker/id1622341132?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T14:02:55.612Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $4.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/isleeper-sleep-tracker/id1622341132?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/21/23/d1/2123d153-d833-8756-eaed-48493c0e10b1/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007epad-0-0-0-1-0-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$4.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  iSleeper only requires your mobile phone to complete sleep monitoring, and can accurately record the user's sleeping habits and sleep cycles through neural network algorithms.

◎ Sleep Recording
We display your sleep recordings on a timeline to maximize the recreation of your sleep. We record various sleep sounds, including snoring, sleep talking,chewing, walking, coughing, sneezing, turning over, sighing, cat meowing, dog barking, bird chirping, and rooster crowing. All recordings are stored only on your phone, so you don’t have to worry about your sleep recordings being leaked.

◎ Smart Alarm Clock
iSleeper alarm on iPhone supports light sleep wake-up, snooze, and voice control to turn off the snooze alarm. We will wake you up when you are in light sleep within the set time range, and you can turn off the snooze alarm with voice control, and sleep for a while until the final alarm rings. The final alarm needs to be turned off manually. (See "Me" -> "Alarm Settings" for details)
The iSleeper alarm on Apple Watch supports light sleep wake-up. We will wake you up when you are in light sleep within the set time range.

◎ Sleep Monitoring
We use neural network algorithms to more accurately analyze your sleep cycle and generate a sleep monitoring chart, which includes your sleep score, sleep duration, time in bed, time to fall asleep, time awake, number of awakenings, sleep goal completion, wake time, REM sleep, core sleep, and deep sleep. If you wear an Apple Watch, the analysis page will generate detailed charts for sleep heart rate variability, sleep heart rate, sleep respiratory rate, sleep blood oxygen, and sleep environmental noise.

◎ Comprehensive Statistics
On the statistics page, you can easily view your sleep trends by week, month, and year. We have also added features for the best sleep day and the worst sleep day, so you can clearly see related information. Understand and analyze the factors affecting your sleep from the trends to improve your sleep.

◎ Automatic Sleep Tracking
If you wear an Apple Watch while sleeping, just turn on sleep mode, and iSleeper will automatically generate nightly sleep records without needing to open iSleeper on your phone.

◎ Welcome to contact us
You can find us in the following ways
- Email: femobisleeper@gmail.com
- Xiaohongshu: iSleeper

I am looking forward to hearing your suggestions. Your affirmation and suggestions are our greatest motivation!

◎ Subscription price and terms
iSleeper can be downloaded for free, upgraded to the iSleeper Pro version, unlocking all paid features (original paid download users will automatically unlock all features)
We provide three different purchase options: one-time purchase, monthly and annual automatic renewal.
Instructions for monthly or annual subscriptions: After confirmation and payment, it will be automatically renewed through your Apple iTunes account. After the deduction is successful, one subscription cycle will be extended. If you need to cancel the subscription, please manually turn off the automatic renewal function in the iTunes / Apple ID settings management at least 24 hours before the end of the current subscription period. During the trial period, if you do not cancel the subscription, the subscription will be automatically activated and deducted at the end of the trial period. This service is up to you to choose whether to cancel. If you choose not to cancel, the renewal service for the next billing cycle will be opened for you.

◎ Disclaimer of health advice
All information and advice provided by iSleeper cannot be regarded as medical advice or diagnosis, and should not replace professional diagnosis and treatment.

◎ Terms of Service and Privacy Policy
Terms of Service: https://isleeper.1008tv.com/terms.html
Privacy Policy: https://isleeper.1008tv.com/privacy.html
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>