<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2025-05-04T23:21:15.040Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:49753370488353792) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:49753370488353792+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T23:21:15.040Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PlayNav - No ads in videos!]]></title>
        <id>PlayNav - No ads in videos!-1746399731721</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/playnav-no-ads-in-videos/id6446178861?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T23:02:11.721Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Premium Features: $2.99 → $0.99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/playnav-no-ads-in-videos/id6446178861?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/fc/ba/1a/fcba1a02-3654-b8f3-5710-7822bcde85d5/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-sRGB-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>Discount Information</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Premium Features：</strong><span>$2.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>$0.99</strong>
</b><span>($0.99 ~ $2.99)</span>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Are you tired of interruptions caused by ads in your YouTube videos?

The new YouTube PlayNav video browser will block all intrusive ads that appear while watching your videos, so you can enjoy your favorite videos smoothly and without interruptions.

Plus, our app offers features you’ll love:
• On-Screen Playback: Watch YouTube videos while using other apps.
• Audio-Only Mode: Listen to any YouTube video with your screen locked.
• Auto Shutdown: Set a sleep timer. (Premium)
• Loop Mode: Automatically repeat your favorite videos.
• Learning Mode: Learn languages using subtitles. (Premium)

It also includes essential features such as playlists, speed adjustment (improved), related videos, AirPlay, and more to enhance your video-watching experience.

» HOW TO USE PLAYNAV?

ON-SCREEN PLAYBACK (PIP) (Premium)

Watch YouTube videos while using any other app. Once activated, the player will shrink on your screen, allowing you to move or hide it with a double tap.

» How to activate it?
1. While playing a video, tap the PIP icon in the upper-left corner (two small screen icons).
2. While a video is playing, swipe up from the bottom of your iPhone, and the player will appear on your screen.

AUDIO-ONLY MODE

Listen to the audio of your favorite YouTube videos with your iPhone screen locked. Use it while exercising, walking, or before bed. Combine it with the auto shutdown feature to relax while listening to your favorite videos!

» How to activate it?
1. Enable On-Screen Playback.
2. Then, lock your iPhone, and the audio will continue playing.

AUTO SHUTDOWN

Bedtime? Find your favorite YouTube video or playlist, set the auto shutdown timer, and let your favorite audio accompany you as you fall asleep.

» How to activate it?
1. Tap the Sleep icon (moon) in the player.
2. Select the time you want for auto shutdown.
3. You can combine it with Audio-Only Mode.

LOOP MODE (REPEAT VIDEO)

Want your video to play on repeat? Use Loop Mode to replay your video as many times as you like. You can also combine it with Audio-Only Mode.

» How to activate it?
1. Tap the Repeat icon. Your video will keep playing on loop until you disable it.

LEARN LANGUAGES WITH SUBTITLES (LEARNING MODE)

Now you can learn languages using subtitles! When you activate Learning Mode, you will see both the original subtitles and the translation in your language. You can also adjust the playback speed to better understand each word.

» How to activate it?
1 Search for videos in the language you are learning.
2 Once your video starts playing, tap the Learning Mode button next to the video title.

– TRY PLAYNAV NOW! –
Enjoy all basic features for free and unlock Premium with a one-time purchase.

Minimum requirements:
• iOS 15 or higher.
• 3G connection or higher.

» Related keywords:
YouTube, YouTube Music, YouTube Vanced, ad blocker, no subscription, skip YouTube ads, ad-free music, block pop-ups, adblock for YouTube, block pop-up ads, ad-free content, premium ad blocker, AdBlock Plus, remove ads, YouTube without ads.

- Need help?
Visit: playnav.vidiom.app or contact us at info@playnav.vidiom.app

Terms of Service: playnav.vidiom.app/terms-of-service
Privacy Policy: playnav.vidiom.app/privacy-policy
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/f4/1b/a3/f41ba35e-2cd1-bfa1-1586-2fad3543c910/e56d11f2-8cdc-4e8a-97a1-8e00a0bdf908_Hotpot_0.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/88/fe/0e/88fe0ed8-2113-5dcd-c7ae-09f39ef6750a/febb8eb4-e913-44a6-829a-bdedac85315b_Hotpot_1.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/18/b3/b2/18b3b206-bb85-4773-a61d-5965a7b0e985/8af986d4-f22c-43a5-8c1c-1c5965a75fa2_Hotpot_3.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/41/0c/84/410c8494-9e93-277d-feb2-af28220e5e97/c7bbd4b7-5d74-42fe-8ee1-858c90270f96_Hotpot_2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/ae/d6/2b/aed62b9b-53dc-59af-3fe5-28e7ecdbd296/6522e8f6-efb0-4ce5-a718-8b1e3079015f_Hotpot_4.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>