<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2025-04-30T16:21:09.244Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:49753370488353792) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:49753370488353792+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:21:09.244Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hero's Adventure]]></title>
        <id>Hero's Adventure-1746028957031</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/heros-adventure/id6711347049?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:02:37.031Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $6.99 → $5.99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/heros-adventure/id6711347049?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/8d/40/ca/8d40ca27-bab9-da59-670a-86064b73d1ff/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$6.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>$5.99</strong>
</b><span>($5.99 ~ $6.99)</span>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Hero's Adventure is an open-world Wuxia RPG developed by Half Amateur Studio.You will commence your journey as an underdog in the tumultuous Martial World and will be met with a wide array of choices as you navigate your own heroic saga.

Game Features

[Unexpected Encounters Await]
Throughout your journey, you will run into scripted and unexpected encounters. Perhaps you'll cross paths with an ambitious lieutenant amidst a power struggle at a humble inn, or you’ll run into a retired kung fu master in a nameless village. These will be the experiences you will learn to expect in the ever-changing Jianghu.

Beware, each encounter might associate and change your relationship with the 30+ factions involved in the power struggle in this chaotic Martial World. And remember: every choice you make, every person you befriend (or offend), and every faction you engage will leave a mark.

[Become the Master of Martial Arts]
Whether you're decoding ancient techniques off a forgotten scroll, or prefer training with a battle-hardened warrior, there’s no correct solution for mastering martial arts. Choose from a variety of weapon types and explore 300+ martial arts skills, the Jianghu will be yours to conquer.

[Explore a Living, Breathing World]
In this Wuxia simulator, you'll get to explore 80 cities and villages that bring wuxia to life. Witness how villagers go about their daily routines, and experience the rhythms of ancient Chinese cities.

[Craft Your Narrative]
To provide an experience where you can embody your own martial spirit, Hero’s Adventure has over 10 distinct endings. Whether you choose to be a noble swordsman, a guardian of the nation, or an agent of chaos, you'll find an ending that aligns with your chosen path in Hero's Adventure.

Discord: https://discord.gg/bcX8pry8ZV
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes Writer Pro 2025]]></title>
        <id>Notes Writer Pro 2025-1746028957031</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notes-writer-pro-2025/id1422480068?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T16:02:37.031Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $9.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notes-writer-pro-2025/id1422480068?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/2c/17/2a/2c172afd-f34c-9a4a-b712-ef25b99cf0fa/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$9.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b><span>(Free ~ $9.99)</span>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  You have lecture notes to take, a story to tell, article to publish, whether it’s today’s journal entry, tomorrow’s thesis, highlight important things in ebooks and PDFs, fill out a PDF form or get the most from your business meetings. Notes Writer is an excellent assistant in study and business, also being effective for writing down your ideas and thoughts and sharing them!

Students, teachers, writers, doctors, journalists, scholars and business professionals use Notes Writer daily to store notes, annotations, memos, signed PDFs, papers, highlighted PDF text-books, lectures and more.

With Notes Writer Pro you can:

+ WRITE. EDIT. FORMAT
· Write Everywhere: Use Notes Writer as an stand-alone writing app even if you don’t have a computer or you are offline in the wilds
· Create rich text format (RTF) and advanced Markdown (MD) documents
· Define margins, headers/footers, paper sizes, MLA and APA style format
· Live counters: characters, words, sentences, lines, Avg. Word length, Words per sentence & reading time
· Text to Speech for proofreading
· Dictation lets you speak text instead of typing
· Typewriter: Distraction-Free mode, letting you focus on what you’re writing
· Over 30 languages typing support including Japanese, Chinese, Arabic & Hebrew 
· Extra keys: tab, forward delete, cursor up/down/left/right, etc. 

+ ANNOTATE PDFs. FILL FORMS. SIGN DOCUMENTS.
· PDF Annotations: highlight, strikeout, underline, notes, voice notes, pencil, stamp, sign... 
· Fill out forms. Supports PDF AcroForms standard
· Sign with your own signature documents, contracts, forms
· Digital Signature Validation 

+ ORGANIZE. STRUCTURE. FIND.
· Organize your work in unlimited notebooks, folders and subfolders
· Create notebooks and projects in your own tree-like structure: Sections, Classes, Lectures, Grades, Drafts, Folders, Chapters, Research, etc.
· Design the cover of your notebooks
· Full-text search your library of documents and projects

+ SCAN NOTES. RESEARCH. PDF LIBRARY
· Split view: Open two PDFs or handwritten notes simultaneously on screen. Compare or use them as book and paper
· Full PDF reader and manager included for reference files, text books, ebooks, articles, resources, papers, etc.
· Use the camera of your iPad/iPhone to scan documents, notes, recipes, tickets, etc. as PDF
· Open PowerPoint, Word and Excel files

+ SHARE NOTES. EXPORT PDF, HTML…
· Open attachments directly from the Mail app
· Sync via iCloud, Dropbox, Box, WebDAV and Google Drive
· Convert to multiple formats RTF, Markdown, PDF, ePub, HTML, RTFD, TXT, etc. 
· Zip folders/notebooks and email them

+ AUTOMATIC BACKUPS. BE SAFE. PROTECT YOUR WORK
· Protect your work with an app security passcode
· Protect any folder or project with a passcode
· Automatic Backups of your notes and notebooks

Notes Writer is more than an innovative, fast and reliable note-taking, PDF annotator and writing app designed for anyone who take notes or writes. This is a smart notepad and writing workspace for your iPad and iPhone.

Privacy Policy
http://www.noteswriter.com/Kairoos_Privacy_Policy.html
EULA
https://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/itunes/dev/stdeula/
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/69/12/1f/69121f7c-bb51-655c-258c-ee00ad6f1b40/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/33/c9/af/33c9af84-5348-3469-546d-92787496562e/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/ca/ec/16/caec16b1-50c8-de59-6dff-aca69d04809f/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/51/cf/7a/51cf7a3c-6c6a-a8a7-d2a6-75b09010021d/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/9a/15/26/9a152655-f290-1576-e7f4-ff25d83341e5/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/57/cf/db/57cfdb85-289f-f76a-ed17-925ca5c01cdb/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/e5/ad/02/e5ad0258-c14e-2b09-4da4-3f72dac89d9c/0abc98c0-34f4-46f6-a6de-32c21345e8f8_SCR1.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/93/89/1c/93891c05-17e7-0d25-9c55-6ce41d5faade/8bcd4c76-b73c-43a0-ba16-5680663bf34f_SCR2.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/df/9a/0a/df9a0a6a-252b-a926-7131-b2e7326ba558/a616772b-b346-4ee2-861c-45ef3366f890_SCR5.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/cc/44/0f/cc440fc9-fed5-d9fd-ac13-f2ba89ea565f/cdf21c1d-cf54-4cd9-abba-87c7720508e1_SCR7.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/c1/05/a3/c105a327-e95a-6e10-d568-bd6f7b5e34a1/cb40be48-3040-4bfa-af83-c06981baf35b_SCR6.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/06/fb/fd/06fbfd83-ef69-1c90-1ad6-7692129e2f71/2f6c2dff-549a-49bb-bf8a-73dad86419bc_SCR3.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/85/e0/38/85e038ef-e954-6b82-382d-33a24641ac21/edf621c5-7342-4762-b04f-8420be881d18_SCR4.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/e7/ff/21/e7ff21eb-05fb-72ff-20a0-1843e9738fe8/703dae60-0e8f-49c3-8bef-0538c28891cf_SCR8.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/ae/5c/4f/ae5c4f5c-5f18-0ca7-4eee-46f2858fb02d/ebc0468e-148b-44af-b750-081d53aa00ca_SCR9.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/a3/06/47/a30647a8-8750-add0-a575-90cb3c0fa21b/f4aadca0-10f6-48e9-92f0-09b709b38ffb_SCR10.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>