<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2024-12-13T10:06:12.279Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T10:06:12.279Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iSleeper: Sleep Tracker]]></title>
        <id>iSleeper: Sleep Tracker-1734084167057</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/isleeper-sleep-tracker/id1622341132?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T10:02:47.057Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $7.99 → $4.99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/isleeper-sleep-tracker/id1622341132?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/b5/56/bc/b556bccc-f75d-1b6d-c917-28b43fc33ef6/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007epad-0-1-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$7.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>$4.99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  iSleeper does not require an internet connection or any other device; all you need is your phone to monitor your sleep. Using neural network algorithms, it can accurately record your sleep habits and cycles.

[Sleep Recording]
We display your sleep recordings on a timeline to maximize the recreation of your sleep. We record various sleep sounds, including snoring, sleep talking,chewing, walking, coughing, sneezing, turning over, sighing, cat meowing, dog barking, bird chirping, and rooster crowing. All recordings are stored only on your phone, so you don’t have to worry about your sleep recordings being leaked.

[Smart Alarm Clock]
The iSleeper alarm clock on iPhone supports snoozing. You can snooze the alarm by voice control and sleep for another 10 minutes until the final alarm rings.
(If you set an alarm for 8:30, with a snooze time 20 minutes in advance, the alarm will ring at 8:10, 8:20, and 8:30. Only the final alarm at 8:30 needs to be turned off manually, while the others can be turned off by voice control. You can set the voice control method in “Me”>“Alarm Setting”> “Turn Off Snooze Alarm”.)

The iSleeper alarm clock on Apple Watch supports waking you up during light sleep. We will find the best time to wake you up during your light sleep phase.
(If you set an alarm for 8:30 with a 20-minute wake-up window, the alarm will find the best time to wake you up between 8:10 and 8:30.)

[Sleep Monitoring]
We use neural network algorithms to more accurately analyze your sleep cycle and generate a sleep monitoring chart, which includes your sleep score, sleep duration, time in bed, time to fall asleep, time awake, number of awakenings, sleep goal completion, wake time, REM sleep, core sleep, and deep sleep. If you wear an Apple Watch, the analysis page will generate detailed charts for sleep heart rate variability, sleep heart rate, sleep respiratory rate, sleep blood oxygen, and sleep environmental noise.

[Comprehensive Statistics]
On the statistics page, you can easily view your sleep trends by week, month, and year. We have also added features for the best sleep day and the worst sleep day, so you can clearly see related information. Understand and analyze the factors affecting your sleep from the trends to improve your sleep.

[Automatic Sleep Tracking]
If you wear an Apple Watch while sleeping, just turn on sleep mode, and iSleeper will automatically generate nightly sleep records without needing to open iSleeper on your phone.

[Privacy Protection]
This application does not require network permissions. We strive to ensure your privacy and safety; your sleep recordings will remain on your phone. This application requires only a few permissions, such as push notifications, microphone access, and access to some health data for reading and writing.

[FAQ]======================
Q: Why is there no sleep recording?
A:  after upgrading to iOS 18, the software will not work after locking the screen.
So please do not lock the screen and keep the screen facing down, the software will enter power saving mode.

Q: Why can’t I turn off the alarm using voice commands like “talking”, “knocking”, or “snapping”?
A: The snooze alarm supports voice control, but the final alarm must be turned off manually. For example, if you set an alarm for 8:30 with a 20-minute snooze time, the alarms at 8:10 and 8:20 are snooze alarms, while the 8:30 alarm is the final alarm. The snooze alarms are gentle and can be turned off by voice control to allow for more snooze time. The final alarm will keep ringing until you turn it off manually to prevent oversleeping.

Q: Why does iSleeper on Apple Watch prompt no background permissions after clicking “Start”?
A: You need to enable background app refresh for iSleeper in Settings -> General -> Background App Refresh on your Apple Watch.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/d4/61/6b/d4616b60-d8f7-fe3c-2356-9a7c864fc179/5ba83e44-c5cd-47ea-91ee-f4d8f38d33b6__U4ecb_U7ecd_U56fe1.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/11/8f/3b/118f3bb7-db8c-aa40-f1e4-1c6cdf83063d/fc8cb606-45ee-492a-bca9-098f8ab9a9c8__U4ecb_U7ecd_U56fe2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/41/fb/ff/41fbff2d-3132-e04d-d5ff-fe8e8645a670/6f8b16a2-24fd-496c-ae88-965e8d0e62f4__U4ecb_U7ecd_U56fe9.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/3d/05/b1/3d05b1c2-96d9-ae76-493b-6e0cff0acb52/87b014cc-08bc-4f42-8ca5-ae77b5c75c8d_jie55en.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/43/9e/97/439e9718-3ac6-dbb5-9c4c-b7d75cd35642/fae09459-c579-43f5-bba2-1435789831fa__U4ecb_U7ecd_U56fe6.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/f9/3c/11/f93c1150-0076-3a93-2bfb-2d6a7503fbb8/aec6ae15-d1d4-4632-b72f-45a6883d4e07__U4ecb_U7ecd_U56fe7.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/bf/6b/de/bf6bdee2-0aa2-0b85-e789-66088a3e3574/_U4ecb_U7ecd_U56fe_U82f1_U6587.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/ae/a2/52/aea25215-a6eb-09db-f139-5914d9f434ca/06b65bf6-630d-4b94-a794-b7b256ef3a92_5.5_enya.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>