<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2024-09-06T03:06:02.501Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T03:06:02.503Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MovieSpirit - Movie Maker Pro]]></title>
        <id>MovieSpirit - Movie Maker Pro-1725591776788</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/moviespirit-movie-maker-pro/id1020541183?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T03:02:56.788Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $9.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/moviespirit-movie-maker-pro/id1020541183?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/58/aa/8f/58aa8fc3-3ede-5036-6576-4f920c5138f3/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-0-0-7-0-0-sRGB-0-0-0-GLES2_U002c0-512MB-85-220-0-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$9.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Pay once, use forever！ You are free to use and upgrade the App in your whole life once you pay for the download once.

Do you want to share your exciting and memorable moments with someone?
Do you want to make your own movie?
Do you want to be a director, a producer, a starring actor?

In MovieSpirit, these characters can all be done by you alone!

With MovieSpirit, you can combine various media materials, such as videos, photos, music, text, recording and finger graffiti, and according to your creativity,  edit them together and add various special effects (scene switching effects, Text animation, Filter effects, video Intro, masks and so on) to create your own movie. 

Main functions:

- Crop, split, merge, cut, transform, flip and scale media clips
- Overlay multi-layers video (Picture-in-picture effect),  no limit to the number of videos or pictures
- Professional Video Ratio, Scalable Timeline (frame by frame), Unlimited Track Layers
- Add masks (Line mask, Rectangle mask, Circle mask, Text mask and Path mask options) to hide or show parts of the video
- Video matting, remove video background
- Cutout Tool (Custom Shape Tools such as Pen Tool, Lasso Tool, Smudge Tool and Text Tool can be used for image matting)
- Replace background for green/blue screen video, chroma key compositing
- up to 50 special effects options, such as Blur, Snow, Rain, Bubble, Flower, Earthquake, Mirror, Fireworks, Smoke, Vortex, flame, Starry Sky and so on
- Gradual Opaque
- Fast-Forward, Slow-Motion and reverse video (1/12 Slow to 16-fold Speed)
- Text-to-Voice function (dozens of language options)
- 360 Degrees rotating video
- Multiple Image Blending modes
- Various fonts, text templates, text colors, vertical text, emojis, shadows, text strokes, alignment etc., supports downloading new fonts from Internet or icloud 
- Built-in free music and sound effects in various styles, adding music from your computer or from iTunes, and extracting audio from videos
- Voice recording
- Draw graffiti with your finger directly on the film, variety of auxiliary drawing shape tools that can be freely selected such as straight line, curve, arrow, circle, square, triangle, star, heart, colorful text and so on
- Simple automatic tracking function
- Add movable mosaic
- Custom Background Color, such as solid color, gradient color and extract color from picture
- Dozens of Animation effects
- Adjustable Brightness, Contrast, Saturation, Exposure, White Balance, Gamma
- Create your own GIF animation
- Private Custom Intro titles (sold separately)
- Up to 80 filter effects (sketch, comics, fisheye, magnifiers, glass, background blur, rotation blur, vortex, various color filter and so on
- Up to 60 scene switching effects
- dozens of appearance shapes can be set for video/picture such as circle, heart, diamond, star, various irregular shapes and even customize unique shapes
- Can turn the video/photo into black and white, highlight the part that needs to be highlighted (Color Splash)
- Free to deform video/photo into irregular shapes
- Add motion points to video/photo/text to make them move, zoom, rotate and move together to create a variety of gorgeous effects, such as fade-in and fade-out effect and up to 100 multiple phantom effect
- Real-time preview, high resolution video output (HD)
- Import multimedia material directly from your computer via Wi-Fi: videos, photos, music and GIF animations
- Save and share videos directly to social networks such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, iCloud, WeChat, Mailbox and so on
- Helpful video tutorials


We're looking forward to any feedback and comments on MovieSpirit, and if you have any query or problem, please feel free to contact us via email verytools2006@gmail.com

We are committed to your long-term satisfaction. Thanks!
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/84/43/c6/8443c612-e66f-2cc4-5404-28496758665d/mzl.vouvntxp.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/81/a6/b9/81a6b968-db10-16b0-7122-fc4bf9a89139/mzl.irrolmav.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/5e/8d/10/5e8d104d-5b8e-8725-b913-0fec3a00d852/mzl.mhpnjkrz.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/55/22/99/552299e2-cf56-fa58-c350-3896ade7ec99/mzl.tasdcgmo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/e5/55/80/e55580c3-ea91-dee0-2e79-6aacfa44eaa6/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/d1/a0/dd/d1a0dd33-42a6-43d9-bd74-e4d1aaf3e727/mzl.gyaqzhtx.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/14/f8/b1/14f8b185-87f3-3d82-6b0c-e34173307848/mzl.zegpdavb.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/f2/8a/dd/f28addfb-74f5-1398-1267-8fb1cabff9e6/mzl.spbtrnit.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/5f/3d/f1/5f3df1c1-daac-1cb8-f8c2-adf671519289/mzl.rkeuxqiq.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/b8/15/b1/b815b16e-b741-2fb6-68f7-7f1a61ac89b5/pr_source.jpg/576x768bb.jpg" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DayCost Pro - Personal Finance]]></title>
        <id>DayCost Pro - Personal Finance-1725591776788</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/daycost-pro-personal-finance/id931188326?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T03:02:56.788Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $2.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/daycost-pro-personal-finance/id931188326?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/b4/51/6d/b4516d63-0c1f-388c-5319-59c9737f5d2d/ProAppIcon-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$2.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Three seconds a bill. Fast, Security and Easy to use is our aim, and iOS notification center widget.

Look at other people how to say:
◎ I just downloaded this app and I am so loving it already! It seems easy to use but I need to explore it more.
◎ Very innovative work. Keep up guys. 5 star app.
◎ It's quick to note down your expenses and helps you track your money.
◎ Polished, smart, simple, with all functions of apps of this kind. Exactly the one I was looking for. Makes me delete other similar apps on my phone and keep only this one, really.
◎ I love this app! It is clean, beautiful, very customizable, and user-friendly. I love the ability to make your own categories and accounts. And I also love the ability to put it in your pull-down Notification Center on your phone. It makes it quickly accessible during the day. Great job, love the app!

Apple Watch:
You can create incomes and expenses from your Apple Watch. The Glance shows your expenses of today, this month.

Feature：
◎ Three seconds only: pull down, fill money, choose category
◎ iOS notification center widget: you can easily account when iPhone lock screen
◎ Passcode security: everyone cannot open, only you. even double-click the Home button, in the App list can not view the data
◎ Support more than 160 kinds of currency, conversion exchange rate automatic updates
◎ Calculator: built-in calculator, more convenient and faster
◎ Full gestures: fast billing basic
◎ Humane beginners guide: for special operations, we guide the way through the animation + text, more intuitive, easier to understand
◎ iCloud backup & restore
◎ Dropbox backup & restore
◎ Export data to CSV via Email
◎ Recurring event, both expenses and incomes, with rich frequency options.
◎ Allow custom theme color and wallpaper.
◎ Allow add transaction from template.

Basic：
◎ Expense & Income bills can be added photos
◎ Income, Expense, Transfer, the others have
◎ Graphical reports, allowing you to easily view the balance of payments situation year / month / week
◎ Budget management: give yourself a reason to control consumption
◎ A variety of color themes and wallpaper, allows you to fully personalize
◎ Custom categories and consumption expenditure accounts, more in line with your needs
◎ Supports iPhone & iPad
◎ Daily reminder

Increase：
◎ Easy copy history through gestures and automatically positioned in the day consumption date, you only need to modify the money can be. of course, you can use the existing money saved directly
◎ You can also add categories and account when billing editing, click on the banner to change currency

If you give up because of difficulties
If you give up because of busy
If you want to know where expenses
If you want to save money
If 。。。

Try our "DayCost" it, she will be your best assistant

URL Schemes: DayCost://

Help translate DayCost:
Contribute to the DayCost translation in your language.
Let's make DayCost available to everyone in the world!
We will show translator's info in DayCost, if you so desire.
In addition, we also give several redemption code as a gift.

have any suggestions or comments, please write to us：support@daycost.com
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/2d/95/8f/2d958fa6-ef62-bbaa-c110-ec6cd43692b4/mzl.kmaesidk.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/99/6e/5a/996e5a12-6650-59dc-7e6b-cb712ba75e53/mzl.gtrysmty.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/ef/3a/4b/ef3a4b71-f5fd-08df-138d-330bbaf75d5f/mzl.vofugzob.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/89/49/93/8949938a-af8c-aa69-4706-f6bd48e3699e/mzl.rmtxxhpn.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/4d/b5/6a/4db56ab8-8873-8706-59f8-8820006978e3/mzl.suesrwke.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/c2/8e/ce/c28ecef0-9360-4fa1-f26c-a3a72badcffd/mzl.sipuksro.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/01/42/08/0142089e-1b73-77e6-5965-2db9628cf134/mzl.tflgjscv.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/93/eb/30/93eb3057-9e8c-8689-5d64-1bb8cfbd090c/mzl.omqysfuw.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/64/4b/90/644b90ab-3d38-581f-a567-1c724e9b8c78/mzl.kschyywg.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RAIN RADAR °- sky weather NOAA]]></title>
        <id>RAIN RADAR °- sky weather NOAA-1725591776788</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/rain-radar-sky-weather-noaa/id488674899?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T03:02:56.788Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $12.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/rain-radar-sky-weather-noaa/id488674899?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/44/a6/eb/44a6ebc2-0045-22bb-5c81-8cbfcc93bfb0/AppIcon-Full-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$12.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Weather radar in your pocket everywhere. 
Use Rain Radar to quickly see an animated radar image and current conditions.

Track the movement of downpours, weather fronts and storms using the zoomable rain radar function. “Rain Radar" forecasts for any location worldwide and displays real-time weather conditions as well as emerging patterns. 

Everything about the weather at a glance. Fast, simple and free of charge! 
A weather forecast app that accurately depicts current weather and emerging patterns.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/a3/3d/2a/a33d2a55-48a0-198c-5b98-6f1dd4cb2126/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/16/b2/96/16b296cb-a323-c26c-1c67-8d336eaade89/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/72/37/90/723790d9-642f-995f-5469-1e588dc81498/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/0d/3f/2d/0d3f2de0-3a41-ebad-bb58-e53b811f4c3d/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/5c/1b/62/5c1b625d-5f1f-e349-1560-7c82a12cf0fe/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/9d/59/61/9d596154-9d65-80c9-ab53-83ffd40e6ef8/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/df/13/66/df13660d-b292-b476-d9e2-e0b2e010d0ba/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/43/88/9c/43889c88-ab93-e998-d855-c08f4fb805db/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/0d/72/7c/0d727cce-b561-e9d2-a7db-3a3de3baa490/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/a3/c4/ea/a3c4ead7-014d-f4c2-af52-4e2eecd97377/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/c7/3b/f1/c73bf143-8967-2204-b939-40b74f669980/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/17/0f/e4/170fe4c4-a239-274a-d507-99efff510706/pr_source.png/552x414bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>