<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2024-11-08T12:06:23.962Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T12:06:23.963Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photomator – Photo Editor]]></title>
        <id>Photomator – Photo Editor-1731067400646</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/photomator-photo-editor/id1444636541?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T12:03:20.646Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yearly Subscription: $39.99 → $29.99<br/>Lifetime: $149.99 → $119.99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/photomator-photo-editor/id1444636541?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/0b/7c/05/0b7c058e-8cdd-3d85-b7e9-2b08cce9b4aa/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007epad-0-0-0-11-0-0-sRGB-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>Discount Information</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Yearly Subscription：</strong><span>$39.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>$29.99</strong>
</b>
  </li><li>
    <strong>Lifetime：</strong><span>$149.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>$119.99</strong>
</b>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Photomator is the most powerful photo editing app ever designed for a mobile device. It includes an extensive collection of cutting-edge color adjustments, automatic selections powered by AI, support for over 750 RAW image formats, a magical Repair tool for removing unwanted objects, and many more powerful features, letting you enjoy pro photo editing anyplace, anytime.

Everything you need to make your photos look incredible
• Edit photos using a wide collection of powerful, nondestructive color adjustments
• Quickly make precise subject, sky, and background selections in photos using AI, add gradient masks, and easily make selections using a brush
• Effortlessly remove unwanted objects using an incredible object removal tool
• Crop, straighten, rotate, and adjust the perspective of photos with an easy-to-use Crop tool
• Instantly increase the resolution of photos using AI
• Remove camera noise and image compression artifacts with the powerful Denoise feature
• Magically remove color banding and increase color depth in photos with the AI-powered Smart Deband feature
• Make your photos stand out with photographer-designed presets for landscape, black and white, and other photography styles
• Easily copy and paste edits between photos or batch edit even hundreds of photographs at a time
• Open and edit over 750 RAW image formats, including Apple ProRAW and compressed Fujifilm RAWs
• Follow all the changes you make in the beautiful live histogram

Tools powered by AI
• Select the subject, sky, or background in a photo with just a tap
• Improve the quality of photos by reducing camera noise with the AI-powered Denoise feature, intelligently upscale photos with Super Resolution, or magically remove color banding and increase color depth using Smart Deband
• Automatically enhance shots using a machine learning algorithm trained on 20 million pro photos, or fine-tune individual adjustments, like White Balance, Selective Color, or Color Balance with a single tap
• Intelligently crop photos using the AI-powered auto-cropping
• Copy the look of any photo to another using the incredible Match Colors feature

State-of-the-art color adjustments
• Enjoy powerful tools for effortlessly adjusting the temperature, tint, exposure, contrast, brightness, hue, saturation, and vibrance in your photos
• Recover incredible amounts of detail in the highlights and shadows of photos
• Magically enhance fine details and structure in photos using powerful Clarity and Texture adjustments, or adjust textures in the highlights, midtones, and shadows separately
• Selectively edit individual color ranges with Selective Color, or improve the balance of colors in the shadows, midtones, and highlights with Color Balance
• Adjust lighting and colors with full precision using Levels and Curves adjustments
• Mix the balance of the red, green, and blue color channels to create intense color effects in your images
• Replace any color with any other using the Replace Color adjustment
• Create beautiful black and whites even from your color photos
• Use a range of additional adjustments, like Sharpen, Fade, Grain, Color Monochrome, Sepia, and Invert to make your photos stand out
• Instantly change the look of photos with LUTs or export custom LUTs to use in other apps

Compatibility
• Automatically sync every change back to your Photos or Files browser
• With the support for iCloud Drive, enjoy seamless edit syncing across Mac, iPhone, and iPad
• Photomator is built from the ground up for iPhone and iPad with a native design that blends seamlessly with the sleek and modern look of iOS and iPadOS 18
• Photomator uses powerful Apple technologies like Metal, Core ML, and Core Image to deliver staggeringly fast performance, even when editing large RAW photos or batch editing multiple images at a time

• Terms of use: https://www.pixelmator.com/terms-of-use/
• Privacy policy: https://www.pixelmator.com/privacy-policy
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/11/cd/43/11cd432c-9665-ea6d-20ad-017ddba078e9/74ef5722-39ac-4c38-85e1-114ae3d1722b_5_U002c5_2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/13/3e/86/133e8613-62cb-550a-6825-ac890527eeb9/cdbd7779-849d-498a-a540-dc86927b77a9_5_U002c5_copy.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/52/f1/d9/52f1d949-43fc-1c17-3d8c-8966c5997034/18bb4aaa-73d1-4c97-821f-47c446342a7d_5_U002c5.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/47/bb/b3/47bbb305-5338-16bc-1e77-4583c385d44e/70d3274b-ff16-44bf-83c2-227001e29669_5_U002c5.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/3b/4e/d6/3b4ed6fc-39ee-392a-fb8e-ec9dd2b40e2c/aaabbb6f-c7f0-4f1b-99ff-9b0eb4a6b815_5_U002c5_3.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/b1/4e/69/b14e6933-806b-a6ae-be4e-1d87847f5977/9ae4baf0-84e2-4ff8-af27-3e3a3919d9be_Workflows.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/65/d1/82/65d182d7-741d-fd46-4a93-58e0eb1c183d/97aa37e5-20f9-45b4-9180-8e8b386f933e_Presets.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/d6/e8/8c/d6e88c0e-5ce5-b38c-62d3-bdcdd4a0c4e9/6f9d0117-bc01-4df6-96dc-c18ca1c5736c_RAW.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/5b/9a/a3/5b9aa31e-ce93-27f7-a9b2-786dee6ae0d1/965dbf72-78f3-4325-855a-774176ddfd5e_Crop.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/c0/4c/14/c04c145c-5aaf-e621-6222-5a74689035c7/c208d809-906c-4010-a6d5-7ad7ea5257cf_5_U002c5_2.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/e4/29/47/e4294755-4348-f39c-91d0-6913309d9205/4451fcf6-0b29-4feb-a574-bf0b5e2ccd45_Appstore_Seni_iPadPro_3.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/2c/91/1f/2c911fa4-b64a-6062-8e0b-c5dbfefcb6e6/5dd55252-f88b-4963-ae61-efa5a138f2a3_Appstore_Seni_iPadPro_5.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/85/4a/5d/854a5d8a-5a53-57bb-7fbd-c9ef4a295ea4/1207d7df-6984-4182-8122-e026f3e2a6ab_Appstore_Seni_iPadPro.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/a7/5a/89/a75a8993-0096-9104-bbaa-dfca47a867c7/fe99086c-63cc-4086-aacb-dbc0b6e151dd_Appstore_iPadPro.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/8b/9d/e3/8b9de3c0-f261-dfc7-86a2-17ae2dd22491/f0382f43-123f-4dd6-92b9-0767a6a11f5b_Appstore_Seni_iPadPro_4.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/dc/e6/f4/dce6f437-e360-bd98-3974-b23921952f1d/0c692fcf-7a4c-4a6a-8e4d-eedcca771708_Appstore_Seni_iPadPro_8.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/30/9d/06/309d06f0-b4db-9523-b940-64fff0d056cb/48a97225-fa74-4de1-a126-859d7a494830_Appstore_Seni_iPadPro_2.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/af/c9/84/afc98450-4bc4-071b-5060-c7b112f9a439/fea1dde7-c049-4118-a78a-83d092a38ee8_Appstore_Seni_iPadPro.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/67/cf/3b/67cf3be2-8f61-a263-4f53-3a50ce0aa6d3/86821e07-cb08-4799-a1e5-a319a2a8039e_Appstore_Seni_iPadPro_7.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/8c/a7/3f/8ca73f6b-085d-e607-7606-98fb4549293e/c736c6b5-3bb4-4162-a085-12c88f21bad4_Appstore_Seni_iPadPro_6.png/552x414bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>