<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2025-01-18T05:05:20.409Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-01-18T05:05:20.409Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodnotes 6]]></title>
        <id>Goodnotes 6-1737176522138</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/goodnotes-6/id1444383602?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-01-18T05:02:02.138Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marketplace Content: $10.99 → $8.99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/goodnotes-6/id1444383602?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/22/f8/6e/22f86ecb-090f-302a-1c0a-e18348774654/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007epad-0-1-0-sRGB-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>Discount Information</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Marketplace Content：</strong><span>$10.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>$8.99</strong>
</b>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Step into the future of note-taking with Goodnotes 6. With leading AI technology and advanced digital tools, Goodnotes is your go-to note-taking app for capturing ideas, organizing documents, sharing notes, and collaborating with others.

Empowering Students to Excel
• Use Ask Goodnotes to get answers to any questions about the information in your notes, generate practice quizzes, and more using AI 
• Solve handwritten math problems anywhere in your notes with Math Assist, simply by tapping the equals sign
• Convert your handwritten math equations to LaTeX format
• Memorize vocabulary, or information from your handwritten notes with Study Sets
• Fix grammar, paraphrase, change length or tone of your text with the the help of AI Typing
• Work on the same document with your classmates in your next seminar or project
• Record audio from your lectures in sync with your handwriting
• Find previous notes in a blink with handwriting search

Enhancing Planners’ Creativity
• Customize the size, color, or cover of your notebooks and paper templates
• Edit, resize, and align your handwriting just like typed text, and watch it reflow to fill the spaces
• Improve your concentration and productivity with Smart Timer
• Download cute stickers, stylish templates, useful paper templates, even educational material from the in-app Marketplace
• Unlimited customizable folders for organizing your notes 
• Bonus downloadable content in Marketplace for paid users every month
• Pencil, tape, eyedropper, elements, lasso tool, crop images, layering, and many more useful features to help you create beautiful notes

Boost Professionals’ Productivity
• Project documents easily from your device and guide your audience with a built-in laser pointer
• Import meeting notes, contracts, photos, presentations, or briefs for signature, annotation or collaboration
• Export your notes to email, print, or share them anywhere as PDF or image
• Add documents by directly sending it to your unique Goodnotes email
• Secure the safety of your important documents with iCloud Sync, Google Drive, OneDrive, Dropbox, and WebDAV

Website: www.goodnotes.com 
X: @goodnotesapp 
Instagram: @goodnotes.app 
Pinterest: @goodnotesapp 
TikTok: @goodnotesapp

Privacy policy: https://www.goodnotes.com/privacy-policy
Terms and Conditions: https://www.goodnotes.com/terms-and-conditions
</p>]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>