<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2025-04-24T04:17:11.203Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:49753370488353792) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:49753370488353792+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T04:17:11.203Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Greedy Cave]]></title>
        <id>The Greedy Cave-1745467358775</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/the-greedy-cave/id1028950091?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-04-24T04:02:38.775Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coupon of the Greedy Cave: $3.99 → $0.99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/the-greedy-cave/id1028950091?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/e5/25/c4/e525c49e-ab0e-e37e-ed0a-5012404bc7d3/AppIcon-1x_U007emarketing-0-10-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>Discount Information</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Coupon of the Greedy Cave：</strong><span>$3.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>$0.99</strong>
</b><span>($0.99 ~ $3.99)</span>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  In a land far, far away there once was a vast continent called Milton. It was a land where the power of rule came by the sword and the arcane, where Men who devoted themselves to the blade or to magecraft, could become the finest warriors, wisest wizards or the greatest adventurers. In this land, there are several kingdoms divided by borders but united through history. Countless stories of alliances, upheaval, and moments of peace bedeck this tapestry, but that is a tale for another day. 

Our story begins in a remote kingdom to the north, Iblis, an obscure and oft-forgotten place. It is a wild and barren land, a place where its people scrape a living from the earth, mining minerals for the lords of the south. On occasion, adventurers would stop by for the night but never linger. Until one day, a fledgling adventurer lost his way and stumbled into a hole. The story might have ended then had he not come back, but return he did, with sacks of gold and glittering treasure. 

Like a fierce gale from the north, news of his fame and fortune fanned across the kingdoms overnight, and kings sent their bravest warriors and adventurers to clear the cavern of monsters in search of treasure. Even peasants wanting a part of this newfound wealth partook in these expeditions. In no time at all, a bustling town had sprung up in this forgotten place. People set up camps, and formed their own groups to explore the cave. Clever merchants not missing this opportunity, built taverns and shops near the cave, selling equipment and potions to eager adventurers. At first, everything seemed fine. As explorers delved into the caves, they encountered new creatures and discovered new treasures. Mysteries continued to pour forth from the cave, yet nobody knew where the source of the secrets lay. However, as the explorations continued, the balance of wealth beyond the cave began to waver, and cracks appeared among those adventurers who had previously worked arm-in-arm. The latecomers or weak, limited to wandering the upper levels of the cave, could only watch as the veteran adventurers brought treasure after treasure from the deep. They began harboring dark thoughts as they watched the veteran adventurers grow arrogant from their largesse, ordering people around, hoarding secrets from the rest. The place became a festering pool of suspicions and greed, mired in a jealous rage. 

It started with an adventurer disappearing in the cave. Rumors circulated he had found some legendary treasure and hoarded it for himself. Others said he had been guided to another world by some mysterious magic force in the cave. Still, the unspoken belief was that he had been murdered by a rival party and was buried somewhere beneath the caverns. Nobody knows exactly what happened, but people have continued to disappear ever since. As more people have gone missing, some adventurers have called it quits, others cling to hope, and a few continue to wait and see. Which brings us to you, an ordinary young man, coming into this extraordinary circumstance with purposes unknown to others. May you find what you seek in ...

--------------------------------------------------------
In " The Greedy Cave", you are a brave adventurer tasked with exploring a mysterious cave and battling all kinds of monsters.

Use your wits to defeat them, learn different skills, gain mighty equipment, challenge evil monster bosses, and decipher the mystery surrounding this cave...

Game Features
·Randomly generated cave levels provide a different game experience every time!                     
·Hundreds of monsters to defeat!
·Hundreds of equipment to collect!
·Hundreds of quests and achievements to conquer!
·Enchant/Reform/Level up/Gold collecting, and more abundant systems to explore!

Contact us
cs.thegreedycave@avalongames.com
https://www.facebook.com/greedycave/
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource112/v4/d8/82/80/d8828029-b4ad-d826-3477-2ef28fab831b/3fe518d5-97e2-47b7-9726-3f8537303757_1242x2208bb.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource122/v4/3c/7b/27/3c7b2770-1da5-973c-601d-5126a080086c/0d0f8b31-e3b8-415c-9298-731a9e04ba17_1242x2208bb__U00281_U0029.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource112/v4/3d/16/5c/3d165c74-7c41-79c9-cb89-fa61498a1765/84f61603-c557-47fb-a32c-50fe07aadb37_1242x2208bb__U00282_U0029.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource112/v4/5a/1e/57/5a1e5738-0143-f680-6c33-4e3a5bbe53b0/1bba7ce0-8a29-43be-a954-33623d955331_1242x2208bb__U00283_U0029.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource112/v4/65/a3/c8/65a3c84c-03c4-6a2e-750b-52e8f7a75531/b29142cf-39ed-4921-a207-bac4de93715a_1242x2208bb__U00284_U0029.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource112/v4/40/30/67/403067b0-2cf8-17fb-8cf3-654f5f18947e/4097713c-e632-4cf1-b79d-cd1cd68bf79b_2048x2732bb.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource122/v4/50/14/3e/50143e10-1086-9a17-0d37-37487a198792/2500cb7b-fab2-4690-b303-61a3d676c2d2_2048x2732bb__U00281_U0029.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource122/v4/61/76/d3/6176d382-b6f0-a650-b081-d098e7864fa6/3ac1f178-06bd-4653-a6b9-b67e6ee45b12_2048x2732bb__U00282_U0029.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource112/v4/80/de/85/80de85df-71f7-9c60-5c46-cd5eb42aff04/dd752b98-76af-49ad-98b2-58fc62bdf6d4_2048x2732bb__U00283_U0029.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource112/v4/cc/b2/56/ccb25637-0099-a2c4-71a2-60f242eaf284/8ab99853-a1fc-4a7d-8bd7-97c8afc3d7a4_2048x2732bb__U00284_U0029.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>