<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2024-10-25T03:11:07.018Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T03:11:07.019Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FyTube - YouTube Without Ads]]></title>
        <id>FyTube - YouTube Without Ads-1729825698341</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/fytube-youtube-without-ads/id1610668825?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T03:08:18.341Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $0.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/fytube-youtube-without-ads/id1610668825?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/52/05/fb/5205fb95-2014-6540-c68c-3105af358cac/AppIcon-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$0.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Our App connects to YouTube in real time and allows you to play any video!
FyTube has special features such as: floating mode playback (while using other Apps) and locked screen playback, as well as other well-known features such as: activate subtitles, change production speed, full screen mode, rewind... we also added filters search by upload dates so you don't miss a single video of the topics you like the most!


SPECIAL FEATURES.

PLAYBACK IN FLOATING MODE:
It allows you to keep your videos playing on a part of your device's screen, while you can simultaneously do any other task with other apps, like send a message, check your email, check your social networks or whatever you want!

How to activate:
1. Choose the video you want to play using our search engine.
2. Our player will open, touch the red icon that will appear to start playback.
3. Once your video is playing, slide our App from the bottom to the top, the player will be in floating mode! you will be able to watch your videos and simultaneously use your device in any other App :) [Check in our preview images].

• Once the producer is in floating mode, you can move it by sliding it, or make it smaller by double tapping.


PLAYBACK WITH LOCKED SCREEN:
This functionality allows you to continue listening to the audio of your videos while your device is on the locked screen, ideal for listening to your music or your favorite songs while driving, or simply when you want to rest with the audio in the background.

How to activate:
1. Activate PLAYBACK IN FLOATING MODE.
2. Then just lock the screen on your device and you will continue to listen to the audio of your video without interruption :)



Need help how to use these features go to: fydub.com/fytube

 
BASIC CHARACTERISTICS:


• Full screen video playback with high quality videos.


• Easy to use interface, friendly design.


• Fast forward and rewind your video whenever you want, never miss the most interesting parts.


• Activation of subtitles.


• Change the playback speed as you like.


• Search engine with smart filters by upload date: day, week, month, year, all.


• In each video you will find the related videos section so you can find more interesting videos.


• Find out about the latest videos and don't miss news from around the world.


• Our App connects directly to YouTube which allows you to find any video.


• Enjoy content on any AirPlay compatible device.


• VoiceOver available.


• Does not require user creation.


• We do not cache, we do not store cookies, we do not store personal data without your authorization, watch your favorite videos safely.


• Interface available in 29 languages.


• WITHOUT ADS INTERRUPTIONS, NO SUBSCRIPTIONS.


GET FyTube IN ONE LIFETIME PAYMENT and start a new video streaming experience with no ads and no subscriptions.


Minimum requirements:


• iOS 13 or higher.
• 3G connection or higher.


Privacy Policy:
https://fydub.com/privacy-policy_fytube


Terms of Service:
https://fydub.com/terms-of-service_fytube


Words related to our application:
youtube, youtobe,youtube youtube music,youtube vanced,youtube ad blocker,no subscription, skip youtube ads, music without ad, music no ads, no ads, app youtube, youtube adblocker, without ads,without ads,block popups,ads remover,pop up blocker,ad-block,blocking ads,adblock for youtube,content blocker,ad blockers,ad blocking,ad blocker,been choice,adblocker,ad-blocker,ad block plus,adblock pro,ad free,block ads,adblock browser,Adblock,ad blocker plus,skip youtube,ads,youtube singing,sin anuncios,music without ad,free you tube red,youtube adblocker,ad skip,block ad,free youtube,video-ads,adblocker youtube,abblocker,stop ads


If you have questions about how to use FyTube visit fydub.com/fytube or write to us, we will be happy to help you, we answer all our emails: fytube@fydub.com

FyTube works with YouTube. The YouTube brand and logo are registered trademarks of Google, Inc. All rights reserved.


© FyTube®.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/02/fd/fd/02fdfdbf-7634-f040-f94f-1f61bd70102c/cf0a4645-e4c7-45bc-80be-ab665a8f6408_IMG2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/a0/91/24/a091243c-47df-7ebb-88f4-773cd9aa3ec1/3899c162-1e28-45dd-bdf2-25d7db7b2f2d_imagen4-ok2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/75/1c/0b/751c0bd8-a7a2-9227-f87f-bde9d019f771/b6243bbd-cf1f-4a6a-8282-268afbb1b5ae_imagen3-ok2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/ed/9a/55/ed9a55af-b448-510c-0197-17027b5949ad/d816a813-16bd-4c0c-9dae-b3007f5a0e15_imagen2-ok2.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safety Photo+Video Pro]]></title>
        <id>Safety Photo+Video Pro-1729825698341</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/safety-photo-video-pro/id456637671?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T03:08:18.341Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $3.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/safety-photo-video-pro/id456637671?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/2b/a1/8d/2ba18d6f-6424-afb5-ddbf-5cd8a1e90b65/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$3.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Protect your Privacy with Safety Photo+Video

Safeguard your private images and videos with Safety Photo+Video. This app ensures that your most sensitive media remains hidden from prying eyes. Take control of your privacy by passcode protecting your personal content, preventing unauthorized access. Conveniently upload new photos and videos from your PC using a web browser or iTunes file sharing.

Discover why you should download this app today!

Have you ever handed your phone to someone, only to find them snooping through your personal pictures and videos? It's frustrating, isn't it? If you want to keep your photos and videos away from prying eyes, Safety Photo+Video is the solution. With this app, you can easily and quickly passcode protect your most private and sensitive media, ensuring that only you have access to them.

Key Features:

• Unlock the app using TouchID or FaceID biometric authentication.
• AI Intruder report: Capture photos of anyone attempting to access your app.
• Decoy password: Conceal your real privacy with a secondary password.
• Enhanced security with dot pattern lock style with AI powered security technology.
• Compatible with both iPhone and iPad; no need to purchase it twice.
• Full support for videos.
• Create personalized albums for organizing your photos.
• Lock individual albums with passcodes.
• Choose from two stylish themes.
• User-friendly interface for effortless navigation.
• Capture private photos and videos within the app.
• Import photos and videos from your device's photo library.
• Export photos directly to your iOS device.
• Move, copy, and paste options for easy management.
• Upload and download files between your PC and iPhone using a web browser or iTunes File Sharing.
• Share photos and videos securely via Bluetooth with other devices that have Safety Photo+Video installed.

With three elegant lock designs, you can customize your passcode style without compromising security. Choose from a standard combination lock, keypad style, or the new dot pattern, all designed for easy access to your personal items with AI powered security system. Each photo album can have its unique passcode and lock design, ensuring enhanced privacy. By directly uploading and downloading files from your PC to Safety Photo+Video, your valuable photos will never land in your camera roll, staying hidden from prying eyes.

Now, Safety Photo+Video supports videos, allowing you to preserve those cherished moments. Import videos from your photo library or capture new ones directly within the app. Organize your albums as you desire, with the ability to move, copy, and paste content. Feeling generous? Safely share your photos and videos via Bluetooth with other devices that have Safety Photo+Video installed.

Download Safety Photo+Video now and take full control of your privacy. Rest assured that anything stored in Safety Photo+Video is for your eyes only.

Visit us at:
Website: https://sixbytes.io
X: https://twitter.com/SixbytesApp
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/sixbytesapp

For more information, please read our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy:
• Terms of Service: https://sixbytes.io/assets/terms-of-service.html
• Privacy Policy: https://sixbytes.io/assets/privacy-policy.html
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/a0/ec/0a/a0ec0ad2-3f52-eec6-cfcb-6b35965fc4a6/c60f616d-e8e1-4588-ab81-2921b2223dc0_1242x2208bb.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/97/11/29/9711292a-da54-5793-76ab-b6b865ef2e2b/87926003-8d66-4281-a6ee-d108eea405ff_1242x2208bb-1.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/59/2c/b7/592cb75b-01cf-4f1e-84b5-16c15411c8c1/f7fe1a1c-4ffe-4b7a-8579-1030c9a7be06_1242x2208bb-2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/cf/92/80/cf928018-c87c-e9b2-3cd9-65c2ea3a17aa/02c3831c-adc4-4509-8229-1b2c17c0aadb_1242x2208bb-3.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/36/11/8e/36118eb6-73d9-e604-7973-dc097659a671/ef085066-7606-4b8c-9087-05cd6d1c3a88_1242x2208bb-4.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/d6/72/77/d67277f5-d380-06d3-272c-246b1c3b5be0/ddd7a7ad-d53e-4cfe-8ef2-ec1db23cc7c5_8.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/ad/f2/f7/adf2f7d0-e79e-d08b-faec-e7bb321b0762/20437d5c-c783-4d67-8520-792472c2ee4c_1242x2208bb-6.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/57/aa/4a/57aa4a5f-ae75-6f37-b773-8ee838dd246f/1c9f9fac-4835-4f7e-8aaa-13c74fdf1553_1242x2208bb-7.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/bf/ca/11/bfca1133-08d4-b4ae-334b-969e79def3b4/21461d0b-54ac-4714-8282-54876ca9230e_1.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/2d/42/c8/2d42c8cc-da97-4ea0-d75e-867302e98f3c/b73819e2-4456-4ba4-baa1-727eca863b74_2.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/62/fc/0b/62fc0bf3-5b27-bd20-1ee6-8b0069c085ee/6244b507-f75b-4ffb-9f2e-9f01d971b9b8_5.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/a3/91/79/a39179f9-9c41-25bb-9d68-fcf7231000cd/87bb3bd0-7975-468e-a47c-759139ba2c07_6.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/5e/c0/07/5ec007a7-5993-d962-ba91-416d2a562ee2/2e56d6c2-b659-480f-907c-c6e9a7f7e92e_7.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/a8/bb/df/a8bbdffa-427e-ca1d-1c25-2329f09378c2/bc03a13b-068f-4865-90c0-88c64113224f_ipad-screenshot.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/62/9d/4f/629d4f0f-df00-002d-cad8-3ddfebd48e43/f9d2e8ea-0130-4d77-8720-14d0ed7c344f_4.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/7b/c1/4c/7bc14c2a-1e7b-79e0-36fe-ac89135e4710/ef01908f-16b2-4504-a807-24f8df5e44ce_3.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juice Watch]]></title>
        <id>Juice Watch-1729825698341</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/juice-watch/id1485101937?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T03:08:18.341Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $6.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/juice-watch/id1485101937?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/04/6e/18/046e1884-3550-6e6f-2483-fef69701fecd/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$6.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Monitor your iPhone battery level from your wrist.

Juice Watch is a simple app designed to do two things well:

• Show the battery level of the paired iPhone in a complication on Apple Watch

• Deliver a notification on your iPhone when your Apple Watch is charging and gets above 90% (or whatever level you choose, from 50% to 100%)

Just glance at your wrist to monitor the charge of your iPhone throughout the day. Or, keep tabs on the battery level of your iPhone while it is plugged in and charging in another room.

You can see both your iPhone and Apple Watch battery levels on the same complication.

You can also get a notification on your Apple Watch when the paired iPhone is charging and reaches at least 80% (or whatever level you choose, from 50% to 100%).

You can set up low battery notifications, to get notifications when your Apple Watch or iPhone battery is low.

Juice Watch is available for a wide variety of complications, so you can use it on your favorite watch faces.

You can also use this app to check your Apple Watch battery level from your paired iPhone. This can be useful while your Apple Watch is charging somewhere else.

Keep in mind that the iPhone battery level shown on Apple Watch is not real-time. It is refreshed periodically, about every 5–60 minutes. The Apple Watch battery level shown on the paired iPhone refreshes at approximately the same rate.

As of iOS 17 and watchOS 10, Juice Watch reports battery levels rounded to the nearest 5% since that's now the granularity that Apple makes available to apps.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/e7/79/05/e77905fd-8531-93f9-7e63-b31ba9d738fd/85dc5c23-12a5-430e-be68-dbbb2066cdfa_5.5_inch_-_1_-_en.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/f6/e1/e5/f6e1e581-ac55-46a4-6a3d-eeabe3789c9f/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/a2/b1/d9/a2b1d958-8649-bd40-7c70-9de4cc49a09a/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>