<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2025-05-01T10:21:09.645Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:49753370488353792) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:49753370488353792+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T10:21:09.645Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bully: Anniversary Edition]]></title>
        <id>Bully: Anniversary Edition-1746093740744</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/bully-anniversary-edition/id1148321705?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T10:02:20.744Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $6.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/bully-anniversary-edition/id1148321705?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/75/5b/0e/755b0edd-6c98-b54e-8dc3-bd1faf8cc4e0/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$6.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b><span>(Free ~ $6.99)</span>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Download and play Bully: Anniversary Edition for up to thirty minutes as a free trial. Purchase the full game as a one-time, in-app purchase to play without any time limits. GTA+ Members can enjoy unlimited access while subscribed for as long as it is included in GTA+.

The Anniversary Edition of Bully has been designed for mobile compatibility and includes four bonus classes and additional non-storyline missions in addition to everything from the original Bully release. 

The Rockstar tradition of groundbreaking, original gameplay, and tongue-in-cheek storytelling invades the schoolyard.  
 
As a mischievous teenager, Jimmy Hopkins, you’ll stand up to bullies, take on the liars, cheats, and snobs who are the most popular members of the student body and faculty at Bullworth Academy — the corrupt and crumbling prep school with an uptight façade — and ultimately learn to navigate the obstacles of life in the worst school around.  
 
If you can survive the school year and outsmart your rivals, you could rule the school. 


Mobile version developed in conjunction with War Drum Studios.
 
Use of this game, including all online features, is governed by the Terms of Service (“ToS”) and Privacy Policy in-game and at www.rockstargames.com/legal and www.rockstargames.com/privacy.  Access to special/bonus/online features, content, services, or functions (“Special Features”), may require single-use serial code, additional fee, and/or Rockstar Games account registration (minimum age varies). Special Features may require internet connection, may not be available to all users or at all times, and may be terminated, modified, or offered under different terms in accordance with the ToS. Violation of the ToS may result in restriction or termination of access to game or online account.  For info, customer service and tech support, visit www.rockstar.com/support.
 
The content of this videogame is purely fictional, and is not intended to represent or depict any actual event, person, or entity; any similarities to real-world places, people, or entities is coincidental and does not imply any third-party sponsorship or endorsement of game content. The makers and publishers of this videogame do not in any way endorse, condone or encourage engaging in any conduct depicted in this videogame.


©2005-2025 Rockstar Games, Inc. Rockstar Games, Rockstar Vancouver, Rockstar New England, R*, Bully, Bully: Anniversary Edition, and related logos are trademarks and/or registered trademarks of Take-Two Interactive Software Inc. Portions of this software are included under license ©2007 Emergent Game Technologies, Inc. The ratings icon(s) and all other marks and trademarks are properties of their respective owners. All Rights Reserved.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/98/75/b5/9875b58a-1bb1-3a14-0e35-3817ac738139/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/f9/b1/0e/f9b10e7f-1691-a094-85de-027a367847fa/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/01/38/ae/0138aeb3-1d4d-9bce-d10d-72cb6f6e8d07/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/dc/88/63/dc88633e-7882-b21b-3354-d138f35bb96f/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/c5/78/0c/c5780c0d-0ed8-2d0c-6e74-e2ad23677672/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/4a/5e/57/4a5e5728-4836-b5a3-3500-06100b39e3d3/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/dc/e2/bb/dce2bb7d-c51f-9171-72f4-292e98edaf90/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/45/36/f8/4536f85c-0636-a24a-005b-a53aa025a5d6/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/84/49/6c/84496c01-4bd4-e523-3ab8-18ac7bfad4c4/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/f4/e4/e4/f4e4e4e3-400e-7340-e4df-352dd044582b/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>