<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2024-11-19T00:12:07.201Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T00:12:07.201Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FyTube - YouTube Without Ads]]></title>
        <id>FyTube - YouTube Without Ads-1731974918473</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/fytube-youtube-without-ads/id1610668825?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T00:08:38.473Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $0.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/fytube-youtube-without-ads/id1610668825?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/52/05/fb/5205fb95-2014-6540-c68c-3105af358cac/AppIcon-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$0.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Our App connects to YouTube in real time and allows you to play any video!
FyTube has special features such as: floating mode playback (while using other Apps) and locked screen playback, as well as other well-known features such as: activate subtitles, change production speed, full screen mode, rewind... we also added filters search by upload dates so you don't miss a single video of the topics you like the most!


SPECIAL FEATURES.

PLAYBACK IN FLOATING MODE:
It allows you to keep your videos playing on a part of your device's screen, while you can simultaneously do any other task with other apps, like send a message, check your email, check your social networks or whatever you want!

How to activate:
1. Choose the video you want to play using our search engine.
2. Our player will open, touch the red icon that will appear to start playback.
3. Once your video is playing, slide our App from the bottom to the top, the player will be in floating mode! you will be able to watch your videos and simultaneously use your device in any other App :) [Check in our preview images].

• Once the producer is in floating mode, you can move it by sliding it, or make it smaller by double tapping.


PLAYBACK WITH LOCKED SCREEN:
This functionality allows you to continue listening to the audio of your videos while your device is on the locked screen, ideal for listening to your music or your favorite songs while driving, or simply when you want to rest with the audio in the background.

How to activate:
1. Activate PLAYBACK IN FLOATING MODE.
2. Then just lock the screen on your device and you will continue to listen to the audio of your video without interruption :)



Need help how to use these features go to: fydub.com/fytube

 
BASIC CHARACTERISTICS:


• Full screen video playback with high quality videos.


• Easy to use interface, friendly design.


• Fast forward and rewind your video whenever you want, never miss the most interesting parts.


• Activation of subtitles.


• Change the playback speed as you like.


• Search engine with smart filters by upload date: day, week, month, year, all.


• In each video you will find the related videos section so you can find more interesting videos.


• Find out about the latest videos and don't miss news from around the world.


• Our App connects directly to YouTube which allows you to find any video.


• Enjoy content on any AirPlay compatible device.


• VoiceOver available.


• Does not require user creation.


• We do not cache, we do not store cookies, we do not store personal data without your authorization, watch your favorite videos safely.


• Interface available in 29 languages.


• WITHOUT ADS INTERRUPTIONS, NO SUBSCRIPTIONS.


GET FyTube IN ONE LIFETIME PAYMENT and start a new video streaming experience with no ads and no subscriptions.


Minimum requirements:


• iOS 13 or higher.
• 3G connection or higher.


Privacy Policy:
https://fydub.com/privacy-policy_fytube


Terms of Service:
https://fydub.com/terms-of-service_fytube


Words related to our application:
youtube, youtobe,youtube youtube music,youtube vanced,youtube ad blocker,no subscription, skip youtube ads, music without ad, music no ads, no ads, app youtube, youtube adblocker, without ads,without ads,block popups,ads remover,pop up blocker,ad-block,blocking ads,adblock for youtube,content blocker,ad blockers,ad blocking,ad blocker,been choice,adblocker,ad-blocker,ad block plus,adblock pro,ad free,block ads,adblock browser,Adblock,ad blocker plus,skip youtube,ads,youtube singing,sin anuncios,music without ad,free you tube red,youtube adblocker,ad skip,block ad,free youtube,video-ads,adblocker youtube,abblocker,stop ads


If you have questions about how to use FyTube visit fydub.com/fytube or write to us, we will be happy to help you, we answer all our emails: fytube@fydub.com

FyTube works with YouTube. The YouTube brand and logo are registered trademarks of Google, Inc. All rights reserved.


© FyTube®.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/02/fd/fd/02fdfdbf-7634-f040-f94f-1f61bd70102c/cf0a4645-e4c7-45bc-80be-ab665a8f6408_IMG2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/a0/91/24/a091243c-47df-7ebb-88f4-773cd9aa3ec1/3899c162-1e28-45dd-bdf2-25d7db7b2f2d_imagen4-ok2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/75/1c/0b/751c0bd8-a7a2-9227-f87f-bde9d019f771/b6243bbd-cf1f-4a6a-8282-268afbb1b5ae_imagen3-ok2.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/ed/9a/55/ed9a55af-b448-510c-0197-17027b5949ad/d816a813-16bd-4c0c-9dae-b3007f5a0e15_imagen2-ok2.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>